<Database>
    <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_PL_DIAGNOSES">

        <LanguageCode>pl</LanguageCode>
        <LanguageNameLocalized>Polski</LanguageNameLocalized>

        <Contributors>
            <Name>capelow</Name>
            <Name>nexusmrsep</Name>
        </Contributors>

        <LocalizedStrings>

            <!-- ============================ -->
            <!-- Diagnoses - Emergency -->
            <!-- ============================ -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PTI</LocID>                         <Text>Tasiemiec uzbrojony</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PTI_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Tasiemce uzbrojone (T. solium) to pasożytnicze płazińce żyjące w systemie trawiennym czowieka. Świnie są przejściowym nosicielem gdy spożywają pokarm lub wodę skażoną ludzkim kałem. Jedzenie niedogotowanej wieprzowiny może spowodować infekcję.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_BTI</LocID>                         <Text>Tasiemiec nieuzbrojony</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_BTI_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Tasiemce nieuzbrojone (T. saginata) to pasożytnicze płazińce żyjące w systemie trawiennym czowieka. Bydło jest przejściowym nosicielem gdy spożywa pokarm lub wodę skażoną ludzkim kałem. Jedzenie niedogotowanej wołowiny może spowodować infekcję.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CKX</LocID>                         <Text>Ospa wietrzna</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CKX_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Ospa wietrzna, znana też pod nazwą varicella, to wysoce zakaźna choroba spowodowana infekcją wirusem ospy wietrznej - półpaśca - Varicella zoster. Choroba skutkuje charakterystyczną wysypką skórną w postaci małych, swędzących pęcherzy, które następnie zmieniają się w strupki.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HRZ</LocID>                         <Text>Półpasiec</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HRZ_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Półpasiec to infekcja spowodowana reaktywacją wirusa ospy wietrznej - pópaśćca - varicella-zoster. Choroba powoduje czerwoną wysypkę skórną w formie małych pęcherzy w szerokim pasie podążającym wzdłóż dermatomu. Półpasiec bywa bardzo bolesny.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ONM</LocID>                         <Text>Grzybica paznokci</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ONM_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Grzybica paznokci zwana też Onychomycosis lub Tinea unguium, to infekcja grzybicza palców lub paznokci.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ATF</LocID>                         <Text>Grzybica stóp</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ATF_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Grzybica stóp zwana też Tinea pedis, to wysoce zaraźliwa grzybiczna infekcja skórna stóp.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_IDA</LocID>                         <Text>Anemia deficytu żelaza</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_IDA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Anemia jest definiowana jako zredukowana zdolność przenoszenia tlenu przez krew. Może to być spowodowane redukcją czerwonych krwinek lub hemoglobiny. Anemia spowodowane deficytem żelaza jest najczęstszą formą anemii.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_LIN</LocID>                         <Text>Nietolerancja laktozy</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_LIN_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Nietolerancja laktozy to niezdolność trawienia laktozy, cukru występującego w produktach mlecznych. Niestrawiona laktoza może powodować wzdęcia, biegunkę i ból brzucha.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CLD</LocID>                         <Text>Przeziębienie</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CLD_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Przeziębienie to infekcja virusowa górnych dróg oddechowych, zwykle nosa lub gardła.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ASN</LocID>                         <Text>Zapalenie zatok</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ASN_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Zapalenie zatok odnosi się do stanu zapalnego jednej lub wielu zatok przynosowych. Zapalenie zatok powoduje opuchliznę i może zaburzyć odprowadzanie śluzu lub ropy z dotkniętej chorobą zatoki.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_APH</LocID>                         <Text>Zapalenie gardła</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_APH_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Zapalenie gardła odnosi się do stanu zapalnego gardła i może być spowodowane bakterią lub wirusem.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ANG</LocID>                         <Text>Angina</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ANG_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Angina to infekcja migdaków podniebiennych. Najczęstsza angina jest spowodowana bakterią Streptococcus pyogenes, i jest znana też jako paciorkowcowe zapalenie gardła.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ANV</LocID>                         <Text>Wirusowe zapalenie gardła</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ANV_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Wirusowe zapalenie gardła to infekcja migdaków podniebiennych, która może być spowodowana kilkoma rodzajami wirusów.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_LAR</LocID>                         <Text>Zapalenie krtani</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_LAR_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Zapalenie krtani odnosi się do stanu zapalnego organu głosowego (krtani). Może być spowodowane bakterią lub wirusem, ale też nadmiernym użyciem głosu.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_INF</LocID>                         <Text>Grypa</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_INF_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Grypa to powszechna choroba zakaźna powodowana przez rodzinę wirusów grypy.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_BRN</LocID>                         <Text>Zapalenie oskrzeli</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_BRN_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Zapalenie oskrzeli odnosi się do stanu zapalnego dolnych dróg oddechowych zwanych oskrzelami i jest zwykle spowodowana wirusem.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HFV</LocID>                         <Text>Katar sienny</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HFV_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Katar sienny, medycznie zwany alergicznym nieżytem nosa, to stan zapalny w nozdrzach spowodowany reakcją alergiczną na alergen występujący w powietrzu, najczęściej pyłki. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ACD</LocID>                         <Text>Kontaktowe zapalenie skóry</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ACD_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Kontaktowe zapalenie skóry to lokalna wysypka lub podrażnienie skóry spowodowane kontaktem z alergenem lub substancją drażniącą.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_GEW</LocID>                         <Text>Łokieć golfisty</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_GEW_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Łokieć golfisty, znany w medycynie jako zapalenie nadkłykcia przyśrodkowego kości ramiennej charakteryzuje się promieniującym bólem z wnętrza okcia w kierunku nadgarstka. Dolegliwość spowodowana jest powtarzającym się ruchem kończyny, powodującym podrażnienie mięści i ścięgien za ten ruch odpowiedzialnych.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_SCS</LocID>                         <Text>Skolioza</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_SCS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Skolioza to boczne skrzywienie kręgosupa zwykle w ksztat litery C lub S. Skolioza jest z reguy bezbolesna.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_RYS</LocID>                         <Text>Zespół Reynarda</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_RYS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Zespół Reynarda powoduje drętwienie i marznięcie dłoni oraz palców u rąk i stóp, w reakcji na zimne warunki pogodowe..</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CFS</LocID>                         <Text>Zespół chronicznego zmęczenia</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CFS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Zespół chronicznego zmęczenia to bardzo skomplikowana choroba odnosząca się do stanu zmęczenia, którego nie da się wyjaśnić żadną leżącą u padstawy chorobą.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_INS</LocID>                         <Text>Bezsenność</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_INS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Bezsenność jest definiowana jako subiektywne doświadczanie trudności ze snem. Może to być spowodowane niemożnością zaśnięcia, lub przespania jednym ciągiem całej nocy, lub zbyt wczesnym budzeniem się.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_ACT</LocID>                         <Text>Kontuzja ramienia</Text>   </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_ACT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Kontuzja ramienia odnosi się do kontuzji tkanek miękkich, bez obecności złamanej kości lub poważnego uszkodzenia skóry lub mięśni.</Text>   </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_HCT</LocID>                         <Text>Kontuzja dłoni</Text>   </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_HCT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Kontuzja dłoni odnosi się do kontuzji tkanek miękkich, bez obecności złamanej kości lub poważnego uszkodzenia skóry lub mięśni</Text>   </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_FCT</LocID>                         <Text>Kontuzja stopy</Text>   </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_FCT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Kontuzja stopy odnosi się do kontuzji tkanek miękkich, bez obecności złamanej kości lub poważnego uszkodzenia skóry lub mięśni</Text>   </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_ACN</LocID>                         <Text>Kontuzja kolana</Text>   </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_ACN_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Kontuzja kolana odnosi się do kontuzji tkanek miękkich, bez obecności złamanej kości lub poważnego uszkodzenia skóry lub mięśni</Text>   </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_LCT</LocID>                         <Text>Kontuzja nogi</Text>   </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_LCT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Kontuzja nogi odnosi się do kontuzji tkanek miękkich, bez obecności złamanej kości lub poważnego uszkodzenia skóry lub mięśni</Text>   </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_CCT</LocID>                         <Text>Kontuzja klatki piersiowej</Text>   </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_CCT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Kontuzja klatki piersiowej odnosi się do kontuzji tkanek miękkich, bez obecności złamanej kości lub poważnego uszkodzenia skóry lub mięśni</Text>   </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <!-- ============================ -->
            <!-- Diagnoses - General surgery department-->
            <!-- ============================ -->

            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HEPA</LocID>                        <Text>Zapalenie wątroby typu A</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HEPA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>            <Text>Zapalenie wątroby jest spowodowane wirusem. Wirus typu A rozprzestrzenia się przez kał i zwykle pojawia się w miejscach charakteryzujących się złymi warunkami sanitarnymi lub słabą higieną.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HEPB</LocID>                        <Text>Zapalenie wątroby typu B</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HEPB_DESCRIPTION</LocID>            <Text>Zapalenie wątroby jest spowodowane wirusem. Wirus typu B rozprzestrzenia się z krwią, przez stosunki płciowe, lub z matki na dziecko.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_EPI</LocID>                         <Text>Niedobór egzokrynowych komórek trzustki</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_EPI_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Niedobór egzokrynowych komórek trzustki występuje, gdy organ jest uszkodzony na tyle, by przestać wystarczająco wydajnie funkcjonować. Normalna absorpcja skadników odżywczych w jelicie cienkim jest przez to upośledzona, prowadząc do niedoborów pokarmowych.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_THD</LocID>                         <Text>Zapalenie tarczycy Hashimoto</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_THD_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Zapalenie tarczycy Hashimoto to autoimmunologiczna choroba, w której system odpornościowy stopniowo niszczy gruczoł tarczycy.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HPT</LocID>                         <Text>Niedoczynność tarczycy</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HPT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Niedoczynność tarczycy to choroba, w której gruczoł tarczycy funkcjonuje nieadekwatnie i produkuje zbyt mało hormonów tarczycy.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HRT</LocID>                         <Text>Choroba Gravesa-Basedowa</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HRT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Choroba Gravesa-Basedowa to choroba układu wydzielniczego, w której gruczoł tarczycy produkuje nadmiar hormonów tarczycy.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_OES</LocID>                         <Text>Zapalenie przełyku</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_OES_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Zapalenie przełyku to stan zapalny powłok przełyku, często spowodowany refluksem.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_OEV</LocID>                         <Text>Żylaki przełyku</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_OEV_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Żylaki przełyku to nienormalnie powiększone żyły w obrębie przełyku. Są zwykle spowodowane nadciśnieniem wrotnym w wyniku występującej choroby wątroby.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HBP</LocID>                         <Text>Infekcja H. pylori</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HBP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Helicobacter pylori to bakteria obecna w górnym przewodzie pokarmowym. Jest główną przyczyną wrzodów trawiennych.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_GAU</LocID>                         <Text>Wrzody trawienne</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_GAU_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Wrzody trawienne to otwarte lezje w powłoce żołądka, dwunastnicy lub przełyku. Są najczęściej spowodowane bakteriami h. pylori lub wydużonym nadmiernym użyciem niesteroidowych leków przeciwzapalnych.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_GAS</LocID>                         <Text>Nieżyt żoądka</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_GAS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>           	<Text>Nieżyt żołądka to zapalenie lub erozja bony śluzowej żołądka. Jest spowodowana złym odżywianiem, nadmiernym spożyciem alkoholu lub nadamiernym zażywaniem niektórych leków. Leczenie obejmuje podanie inhibitorów pompy protonowej i odstawienie alkoholu lub leków powodujących symptomy.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_DUO</LocID>                         <Text>Zapalenie dwunastnicy</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_DUO_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Zapalenie dwunastnicy to stan zapalny błony śluzowej dwunastnicy, początkowego odcinka jelita cienkiego, która ma 12 cali dugości i kształt litery C.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_APP</LocID>                         <Text>Zapalenie wyrostka</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_APP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Zapalenie wyrostka odnosi się do stanu zapalnego wyrostka robaczkowego, który staje się niedrożny i opuchnięty. Rozerwanie wyrostka może być śmiertelne, a zatem zapalenie wyrosktka robaczkowego jest najczęstszą przyczyną chirurgi brzusznej.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CRH</LocID>                         <Text>Choroba Leśniowskiego-Crohna</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CRH_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Choroba Leśniowskiego-Crohna to przewlekła choroba zapalna całych jelit. Dokładna przyczyna jest nieznana, jednakże jest ewidentne, że biorą tu udział czynniki genetyczne, środowiskowe i autoimmunologiczne.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ULC</LocID>                         <Text>Owrzodzenie okrężnicy</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ULC_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Wrzodziejące zapalenie okrężnicy to choroba ze stanem zapalnym jelit skutkująca owrzodzeniem jelita grubego. Dokładna przyczyna jest nieznana, jednakże jest ewidentne, że biorą tu udział czynniki genetyczne, środowiskowe i autoimmunologiczne.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_IBS</LocID>                         <Text>Zespół jelita nadwrażliwego</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_IBS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Zespół jelita nadwrażliwego to chroniczna choroba ukadu trawiennego wymagająca dugotrwaego leczenia. Nie jest zakaźna. Modyfikacja diety i leki pozwalają złagodzić symptomy.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_FDR</LocID>                         <Text>Bakteryjne zakażenie przewodu pokarmowego</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_FDR_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Bakteryjne zakażenie przewodu pokarmowego (grypa żołądkowa) to częsta choroba przewodu pokarmowego, w większości przypadków trwająca kilka dni.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_FOI</LocID>                         <Text>Przetoka jelitowa</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_FOI_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Przetoka to nieprawidowe anatomiczne poączenie pomiędzy dwoma pustymi przestrzeniami.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PER</LocID>                         <Text>Zapalenie otrzewnej</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PER_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Zapalenie otrzewnej to bakteryjna infekcja otrzewnej, membrany okrywającej wewnątrzną ścianę i organy w jamie brzusznej. Nieleczone jest niemal zawsze śmiertelne.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HEF</LocID>                         <Text>Zwłóknienie wątroby</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HEF_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Zwłóknienie wątroby oznacza nagromadzenie się tkanki bliznowatej w wątrobie. Tkanka bliznowata może być rezultatem długotrwaego stanu zapalnego lub innej choroby wątroby spowodowanej wirusami, bakteriami, niedożywieniem, nadużywaniem alkoholu, itp. Nieleczone powoduje marskość wątroby.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CIR</LocID>                         <Text>Marskość wątroby</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CIR_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Marskość wątroby to stan, w którym wątroba nie pracuje prawidowo w skutek dugotrwaych uszkodzeń i zastąpienia normalnej tkanki wątroby tkanką bliznowatą.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CLT</LocID>                         <Text>Kamienie żółciowe</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CLT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Kamienie żółciowe, inaczej kamicą żóciowa, to wytrącenia zwykle bilirubiny, żółci i wapnia, uformowane w woreczku żóciowym. Kamienie żóciowe zwykle nie dają symptomów, jednakże jeśli zablokują kanał żółciowy mogą spowodować wachlarz różnych dolegliwości.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CLS</LocID>                         <Text>Zapalenie woreczka żółciowego</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CLS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Zapalenie woreczka żółciowego to stan zapalny i infekcja pęcherzyka żółciowego, zwykle w wyniku zablokowania przewodu pęcherzykowego (żółciowego) spowodowanego kamieniem żółciowym.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CLA</LocID>                         <Text>Zapalenie dróg żółciowych</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CLA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Zapalenie dróg żółciowych to infekcja przewodu pęcherzykowego (żóciowego), zwykle przez bakterie pochodzące z dwunastnicy. Zdarza się gdy przewód jest już częściowo zablokowany kamieniami żóciowymi.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_APT</LocID>                         <Text>Zapalenie trzustki</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_APT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Zapalenie trzustki odnosi się do stanu zapalnego trzustki. Jest zwykle spowodowane blokadą przez kamienie żółciowe lub nadużywanie alkoholu.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_COE</LocID>                         <Text>Celiakia</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_COE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Celiakia to autoimmunologiczna choroba, w której system odpornościowy reaguje na spożywczy gluten zawarty w pszenicy, życie i jęczmieniu. Reakcja alergiczna powoduje zapalenie jelita cienkiego i spowodowaną tym niedostateczną absorpcję skadników pokarmowych.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ANS</LocID>                         <Text>Zapalenie kłębuszkowe nerek</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ANS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Zapalenie kębuszkowe nerek odnosi się do stanu zapalego części filtrującej nerek. Może być spowodowane infekcją lub reakcją autoimmunologiczną.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TIN</LocID>                         <Text>Śródmiąższowe zapalenie nerek</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TIN_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Śródmiąższowe zapalenie nerek to stan zapalny tkanki miąższowej nerek. Może być spowodowana infekcją lub niepożądaną reakcją na leki.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PNS</LocID>                         <Text>Odmiedniczkowe zapalenie nerek</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PNS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>odmiedniczkowe zapalenie nerek to stan zapalny nerek, zwykle w wyniku rozprzestrzeniania się bakterii z przedwodu moczowego.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ARF</LocID>                         <Text>Ostra niewydolność nerek</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ARF_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Ostra niewydolność nerek odnosi się do nagłej utraty funkcji nerek, sprowadzającej się do zaniku zdolności do filtracji krwi i produkcji moczu. Przyczyn może być wiele, ale zwykle związane jest to ze znacznymi uszkodzeniami tkanek nerek lub zmniejszonym przepływem krwi przez nerki.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CKD</LocID>                         <Text>Przewlekła choroba nerek</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CKD_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Przewlekła choroba nerek odnosi się do stopniowej utraty funkcji nerek. Najczęstszą przyczyną jest nieleczona cukrzyca.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_COK</LocID>                         <Text>Kamienie nerkowe</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_COK_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Kamienie nerkowe, lub inaczej kamica nerkowa, to zwykle złogi wapnia. Mimo tego, że kamienie zwykle same przechodzą przez moczowody, to bardzo bolesna choroba.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_COU</LocID>                         <Text>Kamica moczowodów</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_COU_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Kamienie nerkowe zwykle podążają kanalikami nerkowymi i moczowodami. Jeśli zablokują moczowód lub tylko się przezeń przemieszczają, często powodują nieprzyjemne symptomy.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CIB</LocID>                         <Text>Kamica pęcherza moczowego</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CIB_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Kamienie w pęcherzu moczowym mogą się w nim tworzyć w procesie mineralizacji skoncentrowanego moczu lub mogą być to kamienie, kótre zawędroway z nerek.  Symptomy powodują jedynie te, które blokują przewód moczowy.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ACS</LocID>                         <Text>Infekcja pęcherza moczowego</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ACS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Infekcja pęcherza moczowego to infekcja pęcherza spowodowana zwykle bakterią pałeczki okrężnicy (E. coli), typem bakterii często występującej w przewodzie pokarmowym. To choroba sto razy częściej występująca u kobiet niż u mężczyzn.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_INC</LocID>                         <Text>Śródmiąższowe zapalenie pęcherza moczowego</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_INC_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Śródmiąższowe zapalenie pęcherza moczowego zwane jest też zespołem bolesnego pęcherza. To choroba pęcherza o nieustalonej przyczynie dotykająca bardziej kobiet niż mężczyzn.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_LIP</LocID>                         <Text>Rozdarcie wątroby</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_LIP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Rozdarcie wątroby to rana, która powstaje gdy obiekt przebija skórę górnej części brzucha i wnika w tkanki ciała, tworząc otwartą ranę i uszkodzenie wątroby.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_LIB</LocID>                         <Text>Kontuzja wątroby</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_LIB_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Kontuzja wątroby to fizyczny uraz górnej części brzucha, czy to w skutek uderzenia, zranienia lub fizycznego ataku.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SRB</LocID>                         <Text>Kontuzyjne pęknięcie śledziony</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SRB_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Kontuzyjne pęknięcie śledziony jest spowodowane tępym uderzeniem, zranieniem lub atakiem fizycznym, ale bez obecności otwartej rany.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SRP</LocID>                         <Text>Pęknięcie śledziony</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SRP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Pęknięcie śledziony w skutek przebicia występuje gdy obiekt przebija skórę górnej części brzucha i wnika w tkanki ciała, powodując otwartą ranę i rozległe uszkodzenie śledziony.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SCB</LocID>                         <Text>Obtłuczona śledziona</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SCB_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Zwana też kontuzją śledziony, spowodowana bezpośrednim uderzeniem w górną część brzucha. Jest mniej poważna od pęknięcia śledziony.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_PCB</LocID>                         <Text>Kontuzja trzustki</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_PCB_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Pomniejsza kontuzja trzustki bez urazów przewodów z obecnością krwiaka. Jest spowodowana bezpośrednim uderzeniem bez przebicia skóry.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_PLB</LocID>                         <Text>Kontuzyjne rozerwanie trzustki</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_PLB_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Poważne rozerwanie trzustki z towarzyszącymi ranami przewodów spowodowane bezpośrednim uderzeniem w brzuch, bez otwartej rany jamy brzusznej.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_PCP</LocID>                         <Text>Rozerwanie trzustki</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_PCP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Masywne uszkodzenie głowy trzustki spowodowane raną i przebiciem górnych powłok brzusznych.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_KLP</LocID>                         <Text>Rozerwanie nerek</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_KLP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Poważne obrażenia miękiszu gąbczastego nerek z obecnością zaotrzewnowego krwiaka i otwartą raną pleców.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_KCB</LocID>                         <Text>Kontuzja nerek</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_KCB_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Obtłuczenie nerek wraz z (lub bez) nie rozszerzającym się podtorebkowym krwiakiem.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <!-- ======================================== -->
            <!-- Diagnoses - Internal medicine department -->
            <!-- ======================================== -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CLC</LocID>                         <Text>Classical cholera</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CLC_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Cholera is a bacterial disease usually spread through contaminated water supplies. Modern sewage and water treatment eliminated cholera in industrialized countries.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TYF</LocID>                         <Text>Typhoid fever</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TYF_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Typhoid fever is bacterial disease and spreads through contaminated water and food. Also it is contagious. In industrialized countries it is rare.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_SLM</LocID>                         <Text>Salmonellosis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_SLM_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Salmonella infection is one one of the common bacterial infection that affects human intestinal tract. Human gets infected through contaminated water or food. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_AMB</LocID>                         <Text>Amoebiasis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_AMB_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Amoebiasis is caused by Entamoeba histolytica, the infection spreads through water or food contaminated by feces.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_GRD</LocID>                         <Text>Giardiasis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_GRD_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Giardia infection is one of the most common waterborne intestinal infections. Giardias can be transmitted also through personal contact or through food.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TBC</LocID>                         <Text>Tuberculosis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TBC_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Tuberculosis of the lungs is highly contagious disease caused by bacteria Mycobacterium tuberculosis affecting principally lungs, but can affect also another organs. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TUL</LocID>                         <Text>Tularaemia</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TUL_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Tularaemia is an infectious disease that affects mainly skin, eyes, lymph nodes and lungs. It is caused by the bacteria known as Francisella tularensis. Tulareamia is highly contagious, potentially fatal, but can be treated effectively.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PNA</LocID>                         <Text>Pulmonary anthrax</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PNA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Anthrax is serious infection caused by the bacterium known as Bacillus anthracis. It is spread through the spores, which are usually by animal origin. Contact is made typically by breathing, eating or through the skin lesion.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_RBF</LocID>                         <Text>Rat-bite fever</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_RBF_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Rat-bite fever is acute febrile disease caused by bacteria transmitted by rodents, particularly by their urine or mucous secretions. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CSD</LocID>                         <Text>Cat-scratch disease</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CSD_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Cat-scratch disease is a common infectious disease caused by Bartonella henselae. It is transmitted through cats, respectively through the cat's scratch or bite. Presence of the bacteria in human is hard to detect by usual methods of cultivation, because growth takes up to 6 weeks.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PMI</LocID>                         <Text>Pulmonary NTMB infection</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PMI_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Pulmonary mycobacterial infection of nontuberculous type is caused by mycobacterium and it is relatively common. Often occuring in patients with depressed imunity or with preexisting pulmonary disease, but also in healthy patients.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PTS</LocID>                         <Text>Pertussis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PTS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Pertussis also known as Whooping Cough is highly contagious respiratory disease. It is caused by bacteria known as Bordetella pertussis. Before development of a vaccine, pertussis was considered a childhood disease. Now it affects people whose immunity has decreased.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_LEG</LocID>                         <Text>Legionnaires disease</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_LEG_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Legionnaires disease is caused by the bacterium Legionella pneumophila. The disease is severe form of pneumonia, transmitting through person to person. Untreated Legionnaires diseases has fatal consequences.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TPF</LocID>                         <Text>Typhus fever</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TPF_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>It is important not to be confused with Typhoid fever. Typhus is caused by the bacteria Rickettsia Typhi, transmitted through various types of fleas. Typhus has been decscribed since 1528. It has sudden onset of various symptoms comparable to flu.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_IMN</LocID>                         <Text>Infectious mononucleosis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_IMN_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Infectious mononucleosis is usually caused by EBV - Epstein-Barr Virus, people usually get infected in the childhood and when they grow up, symptoms will present. There is no vaccine for the disease. In 1920's it was described as "the kissing disease".</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HPM</LocID>                         <Text>Histoplasmosis </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HPM_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Histoplasmosis also called Cave Disease is respiratory disease caused by fungus Histoplasma Capsulatum affecting mainly the lungs. Symptoms vary greatly. Past infection creates partial protection. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ASP</LocID>                         <Text>Aspergillosis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ASP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Aspergillosis is respiratory disease caused by fungus Aspergillus. If patient has weakened immune system, invasive form of the disease spreads through the lungs. Compromised lungs must undergo pulmonary surgery.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ATS</LocID>                         <Text>American trypanosomias</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ATS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>American trypanosomias also known as Chagas disease is serious inflammatory infectious disease caused by the parasite Trypanosoma cruzi. If left untreated, can do serious heart and digestive complications.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TXM</LocID>                         <Text>Toxoplasmosis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TXM_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Toxoplasmosis is caused due to the parasite known as Toxoplasma gondii. Symptoms are similar to common flu. Infections is spread through undercooked food, exposure to cat's feces.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_BAB</LocID>                         <Text>Babesiosis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_BAB_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Babesiosis is parasitic disease caused due to the parasite Babesia. It is comparable to malaria. Strain of transmit is through ticks, often presented with Lyme disease.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_LYD</LocID>                         <Text>Lyme disease</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_LYD_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Lyme disease is  caused by the bite of a deer tick or back-legged tick. It can transfer a form of bacteria  Borrelia burgdorferi which directly causes disease.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HLA</LocID>                         <Text>Hemolytic anemia</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HLA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Hemolytic anemia happens when there is undergoing hemolysis - abnormal breakdown of red blood cells in the blood vessels or elsewhere in the human body.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TCP</LocID>                         <Text>Thrombocytopenia</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TCP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Thrombocytopenia represents a condition with significantly fewer amounts of blood platelets, that are responsible for stopping bleeding by clumping and forming plugs.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HPL</LocID>                         <Text>Hemophilia</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HPL_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Hemophilia is an inherited disease that causes low levels of clotting factors. Blood then does not clot properly which leads to excessive bleeding.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_THL</LocID>                         <Text>Thalassaemia</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_THL_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Thalassaemia is an inherited blood disorder with significant less hemoglobin and fewer red blood cells.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_SRCL</LocID>                        <Text>Sarcoidosis - Lungs</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_SRCL_DESCRIPTION</LocID>            <Text>Sarcoidosis is growth of granulomas (inflammatory cells) in various parts of the human body. Most probably it is because of the immune reaction to some agents. There is no cure, but with supporting medicine the disease can pass.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_SRCE</LocID>                        <Text>Sarcoidosis - Eye</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_SRCE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>            <Text>Sarcoidosis is growth of granulomas (inflammatory cells) in various parts of the human body. Most probably it is because of the immune reaction to some agents. There is no cure, but with the supporting medicine the disease can pass.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_SRCH</LocID>                        <Text>Sarcoidosis - Heart</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_SRCH_DESCRIPTION</LocID>            <Text>Sarcoidosis is growth of granulomas (inflammatory cells) in various parts of the human body. Most probably it is because of the immune reaction to some agents. There is no cure, but with the supporting medicine the disease can pass.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_DM1</LocID>                         <Text>Diabetes</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_DM1_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Diabetes mellitus refers to a group of diseases that affecting metabolism of glucose. There are many types of diabetes, but generally there is too high level of glucose in blood.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CFB</LocID>                         <Text>Cystic fibrosis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CFB_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Cystic fibrosis is an inherited disease that produces serious damage to lungs, digestive system and other organs of the human body.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_OTE</LocID>                         <Text>Otitis externa</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_OTE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Otitis externa is inflammation of the outer part of the ear canal, it is caused mostly due to bacteria.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_OME</LocID>                         <Text>Otitis media</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_OME_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Otitis media with effusion is the condition where fluid is present in the middle ear. It usually affects children.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ASO</LocID>                         <Text>ASOM</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ASO_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Acute suppurative otitis media is a very painful inflammation of the middle ear.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_AMT</LocID>                         <Text>Acute mastoiditis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_AMT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Mastoiditis refers to infection and inflammation of mastoid cells located in the mastoid process in the temporal bone (beneath the ear). </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_OTS</LocID>                         <Text>Otosclerosis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_OTS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Otosclerosis refers to abnormal hardening of the bone tissue near the middle ear causing inability to transfer sounds from the middle ear to the inner ear; resulting in loss of hearing.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_OOR</LocID>                         <Text>Otorrhea</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_OOR_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Otorrhea is basically an inflammation or the ear.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_MUM</LocID>                         <Text>Mumps</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_MUM_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Mumps also known as Parotitis, is an inflammatory, infectious disease affecting parotid glands (on one or on the both sides of the human face). Inflammation is caused by bacterial or viral agents. Best prevention is vaccination.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PNM</LocID>                         <Text>Pneumonia</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PNM_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Pneumonia is an infection of the air sacs in the lungs. Pneumonia ranges from mild to life threatening.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_BPN</LocID>                         <Text>Bronchopneumonia</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_BPN_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Bronchopneumonia is disease from the lung category infections, it is also known as lobular pneumonia. It affects the lungs and bronchi.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_BES</LocID>                         <Text>Bronchiectasis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_BES_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Bronchiectasis refers to condition where the large airways in the lungs are damaged.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_SCB</LocID>                         <Text>Simple chronic bronchitis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_SCB_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Chronic bronchitis refers to productive long-lasting cough along with constant irritation of the bronchial lining.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_EMP</LocID>                         <Text>Emphysema</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_EMP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Emphysema refers to a condition when the alveoli - the air sacs - are damaged or destroyed, causing shortness of breath, even in states of relaxation.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CPD</LocID>                         <Text>COPD</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CPD_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Chronic obstructive pulmonary disease - COPD is a chronic inflammatory lung disease that causes obstructed airways from the lungs.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ASM</LocID>                         <Text>Asthma</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ASM_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Asthma refers to a condition where airways narrow, swell and produce extra mucus. It is a chronic respiratory disease and symptoms may vary from person to person.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PMX</LocID>                         <Text>Pneumothorax</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PMX_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Collapsed lung also called pneumothorax occurs when air escapes lung filling the space between lung and chest wall, preventing expansion of the affected lung.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CEL</LocID>                         <Text>Cellulitis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CEL_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Cellulitis is one of the common bacterial skin infections caused mostly by streptococci and staphylococci.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ADS</LocID>                         <Text>Atopic dermatitis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ADS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Atopic dermatitis or eczema refers to a condition that makes skin reddish and itchy. It is chronic skin disease.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_LUP</LocID>                         <Text>Lupus</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_LUP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Lupus is a systemic autoimmune disease. It is very difficult to diagnose.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_CMP</LocID>                         <Text>CO poisoning</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_CMP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Carbon monoxide poisoning typically occurs from breathing in too much carbon monoxide.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_CGP</LocID>                         <Text>Chlorine gas poisoning</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_CGP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Chlorine gas poisoning is an illness resulting from the effects of exposure to chlorine beyond the threshold limit value.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_MTP</LocID>                         <Text>Methanol poisoning</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_MTP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Methanol ingestion is an uncommon form of poisoning that can cause severe metabolic disturbances, blindness, permanent neurological dysfunction and death.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_LDP</LocID>                         <Text>Lead poisoning</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_LDP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Lead poisoning is a type of metal poisoning caused by accumulated lead in the body.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_PCT</LocID>                         <Text>Contused lungs</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_PCT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Blunt injury or physical trauma to a body part, either by impact, injury or physical attack. Pulmonary contusion is present.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_PLP</LocID>                         <Text>Pulmonary laceration</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_PLP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Penetrating trauma is an injury that occurs when an object pierces the skin and enters a tissue of the body, creating an open wound. Pulmonary laceration is present.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <!-- ====================================== -->
            <!-- Diagnoses - Orthopaedy -->
            <!-- ====================================== -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CTS</LocID>                         <Text>Carpal tunnel syndrome</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CTS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>A condition where the median nerve is compressed by surrounding structures when passing through the tunnel near the base of the palm. Pain and disturbed sensation are the main symptoms. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CUS</LocID>                         <Text>Cubital tunnel syndrome</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CUS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Cubital tunnel syndrome is caused by the compression of the ulnar nerve in the elbow area.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_RAT</LocID>                         <Text>Rheumatoid arthritis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_RAT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Rheumatoid arthritis is a chronic autoimmune disease affecting primarily joints. It typically results in warm, swollen, and painful joints. Pain and stiffness often worsen following rest. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HOA</LocID>                         <Text>Hip osteoarthritis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HOA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Osteoarthritis is a condition where cartilage slowly degenerates and deformities arise in the affected joint. Hip osteoarthritis typically makes walking painful and cumbersome.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_KOA</LocID>                         <Text>Knee osteoarthritis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_KOA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Knee Osteoarthritis is one of the most common types of arthritis. A slow degradation of the knee cartilage causes pain when walking and stiffness of the joint.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_DMS</LocID>                         <Text>Dermatomyositis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_DMS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Dermatomyositis is chronic progressive inflammation of the muscles. Symptoms are usually a skin rash and increased muscle weakness over time.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_IBM</LocID>                         <Text>Inclusion-body myositis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_IBM_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Inclusion-body myositis is chronic progressive inflammation and weakening of the muscles. It is most apparent the finger flexor and knee extensor muscles.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PMS</LocID>                         <Text>Polymyositis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PMS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Polymyositis is chronic progressive inflammation and weakening of the muscles. It begins with weakness in the muscles closest to the body trunk from where it spreads.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_SDS</LocID>                         <Text>Spondylolysis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_SDS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Spondylolysis is a defect, crack or stress fracture in one of the vertebrae, typically in the L5-S1 level. The condition can be painful. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_SDL</LocID>                         <Text>Spondylolisthesis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_SDL_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Spondylolisthesis refers to a displaced vertebrae. Several conditions can cause spondylolisthesis; degenerative changes, trauma, congenital abnormalities, malignancy etc.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CSL</LocID>                         <Text>Cervical spondylosis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CSL_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Cervical spondylosis is a degeneration of the cervical spine frmo any cause. Often it is synonymous with age-related wear and tear causing spinal osteoarthritis.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_OSM</LocID>                         <Text>Acute osteomyelitis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_OSM_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Acute osteomyelitis is a bacterial infection of the bone. It can develop into chronic osteomyelitis which is very difficult to treat.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CDD</LocID>                         <Text>Spinal stenosis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CDD_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Spinal stenosis refers to an abnormal narrowing of the spinal canal, which affects the spinal cord or nerve roots. It causes pain, discomfort and loss of mobility usually in the limbs corresponding to the level of the stenosis.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_BOT</LocID>                         <Text>Knee bursitis </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_BOT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>A bursae is a small fluid filled sac which acts as a cushion between bone and areas prone to friction. Bursitis refers to swelling of said sac caused by inflammation.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_BOH</LocID>                         <Text>Hand bursitis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_BOH_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>A bursae is a small fluid filled sac which acts as a cushion between bone and areas prone to friction. Bursitis refers to swelling of said sac caused by inflammation</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_AOM</LocID>                         <Text>Osteomalacia</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_AOM_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Osteomalacia, known as Rickets if it occurs in childhood, refers to a condition where the bones soften due to impaired bone metabolism.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TEW</LocID>                         <Text>Tennis elbow</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TEW_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Tennis elbow, also known as lateral epicondylitis, is characterized by radiating pain from the outside of the elbow to the wrist. The condition is caused by performing repetitive movement and, thus, irritation of the muscles and tendons associated with said movement.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_OLB</LocID>                         <Text>Elbow bursitis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_OLB_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>A bursae is a small fluid filled sac which acts as a cushion between bone and areas prone to friction. Bursitis refers to swelling of said sac caused by inflammation.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_DWH</LocID>                         <Text>Deep wound on hand</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_DWH_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>A bleeding deep, smooth or jagged wound. It needs suturing.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_DWA</LocID>                         <Text>Deep wound on arm</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_DWA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>A bleeding deep, smooth or jagged wound. It needs suturing.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_DWL</LocID>                         <Text>Deep wound on leg</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_DWL_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>A bleeding deep, smooth or jagged wound. It needs suturing..</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_DWF</LocID>                         <Text>Deep wound on feet</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_DWF_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>A bleeding deep, smooth or jagged wound. It needs suturing.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SHS</LocID>                         <Text>Shoulder sprain</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SHS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>A sprain is a condition where a ligament surrounding a joint is taken beyond its functional range of motion, causing tears and sometimes to complete rupture of the affected ligaments.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SHD</LocID>                         <Text>Shoulder dislocation</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SHD_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Joint dislocation, also known as luxation, is a condition where the bones connected by a joint are abnormally separated. Damage to the adjacent tissue is common.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_KSP</LocID>                         <Text>Knee sprain</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_KSP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>A sprain is a condition where a ligament surrounding a joint is taken beyond its functional range of motion, causing tears and sometimes to complete rupture of the affected ligaments.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_KDL</LocID>                         <Text>Knee dislocation</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_KDL_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Joint dislocation, also known as luxation, is a condition where the bones connected by a joint are abnormally separated. Damage to the adjacent tissue is common.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_ASP</LocID>                         <Text>Ankle sprain</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_ASP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>A sprain is a condition where a ligament surrounding a joint is taken beyond its functional range of motion, causing tears and sometimes to complete rupture of the affected ligaments.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_DLA</LocID>                         <Text>Dislocated ankle</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_DLA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Joint dislocation, also known as luxation, is a condition where the bones connected by a joint are abnormally separated. Damage to the adjacent tissue is common.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_ACL</LocID>                         <Text>ACL injury</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_ACL_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>The Anterior Cruciate Ligament, is a ligament located inside the knee joint that prevents forward displacement between the leg bones. Injury to this ligament is common in sports and is caused by abnormal inward rotation.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SFU</LocID>                         <Text>Simple fracture of ulna</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SFU_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Fracture of ulna, one of the two bones in the forearm, without damage to the surrounding tissues or breaking of the skin.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_OFU</LocID>                         <Text>Open fracture of ulna</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_OFU_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Open fracture, also called compound fracture, is a fracture resulting in an open wound, cause by the dislocated bone, often with bone protruding through the wound. Ulna is one of the two bones in the forearm.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_CFU</LocID>                         <Text>Complicated fracture of ulna</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_CFU_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Complicated fracture consists of open wound, dislocated fractured bone and various fragments of broken bone. Ulna is one of the two bones in the forearm.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SFR</LocID>                         <Text>Simple fracture of radius</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SFR_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Fracture of radius, one of the two bones in the forearm, without damage to the surrounding tissues or breaking of the skin.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SFH</LocID>                         <Text>Simple fracture of humerus</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SFH_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Fracture of humerus, the bone in the upper arm, without damage to the surrounding tissues or breaking of the skin.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_OFH</LocID>                         <Text>Open fracture of humerus</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_OFH_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Open fracture, also called compound fracture, is a fracture resulting in an open wound, cause by the dislocated bone, often with bone protruding through the wound. Humerus is the bone in the upper arm.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_CFH</LocID>                         <Text>Complicated fracture of humerus</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_CFH_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Complicated fracture consists of open wound, dislocated fractured bone and various fragments of broken bone. Humerus is the bone in the upper arm.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_BRR</LocID>                         <Text>Broken ribs</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_BRR_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Simple fracture of one or more ribs with no damage to surrounding tissues or breaking of the skin.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SFF</LocID>                         <Text>Simple fracture of femur</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SFF_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Fracture of the femur, the bone in the thigh, without damage to the surrounding tissues or breaking of the skin.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_OFF</LocID>                         <Text>Open fracture of femur</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_OFF_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Open fracture, also called compound fracture, is a fracture resulting in an open wound, cause by the dislocated bone, often with bone protruding through the wound. The femur is the bone in the thigh.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_CFF</LocID>                         <Text>Complicated fracture of femur</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_CFF_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Complicated fracture consists of open wound, dislocated fractured bone and various fragments of broken bone. The femur is the bone in the thigh.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SFT</LocID>                         <Text>Simple fracture of tibia</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SFT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Fracture of tibia, the large bone in the lower leg, without damage to the surrounding tissues or breaking of the skin.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_OFT</LocID>                         <Text>Open fracture of tibia</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_OFT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Open fracture, also called compound fracture, is a fracture resulting in an open wound, cause by the dislocated bone, often with bone protruding through the wound. Tibia is the large bone in the lower leg.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SPT</LocID>                         <Text>Spiral fracture of tibia</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SPT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Special spiral fracture of tibia bone, with no damage to surrounding tissues.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SFI</LocID>                         <Text>Simple fracture of fibula</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SFI_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Fracture of fibula, the thin bone in the lower leg, without damage to the surrounding tissues or breaking of the skin.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_ANF</LocID>                         <Text>Ankle fracture</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_ANF_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Fracture of one or more bones of the ankle, without damage to the surrounding tissues.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_MBF</LocID>                         <Text>Metatarsal bones fracture</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_MBF_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Fracture of one or more metatarsal bones, without damage to the surrounding tissues.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_FOF</LocID>                         <Text>Fracture of finger</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_FOF_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Fracture of one or more of the finger bones, without damage to the surrounding tissues.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SFC</LocID>                         <Text>Simple fracture of clavicle</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SFC_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Fracture of the clavicle without damage to the surrounding tissues or breaking of the skin.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SHC</LocID>                         <Text>Shaft fracture of clavicle</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_SHC_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Fracture of the clavicle with dislocation of part of the fractured bone.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_MNF</LocID>                         <Text>Mandibular fracture</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_MNF_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Fracture of the jaw. Often includes a break in two places. Usually causes decreased ability to open the mouth fully.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_NSF</LocID>                         <Text>Nasal fracture</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_NSF_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Simple fracture of one or more nasal bones with some bleeding present.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <!-- ===================== -->
            <!-- Diagnoses - Cardiology-->
            <!-- ===================== -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ARR</LocID>                         <Text>Acute rheumatic fever</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ARR_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Acute rheumatic fever is an inflammatory disease affecting the heart, muscles, joints and the brain. Usually it develops after a simple streptococcal infection of the throat.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_MST</LocID>                         <Text>Mitral stenosis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_MST_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Mitral valve stenosis is a narrowing of the heart's mitral valve, that causes improper opening of the valve and thereby the blood flow through the valve is reduced.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TRS</LocID>                         <Text>Tricuspid regurgitation</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TRS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Improper closening of the heart's tricuspid valve, resulting in the regurgitation of blood (blood is pumped backwards, the wrong direction, because the valve can't close properly).</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HHD</LocID>                         <Text>HHD with heart failure</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HHD_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Hypertensive heart disease refers to multiple complications related to high blood pressure that affects the heart and can result in heart failure.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_IHD</LocID>                         <Text>IHD with heart failure</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_IHD_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Ischaemic heart disease, also known as coronary artery disease, is large group of cardiovascular diseases caused by the atherosclerosis of the coronary arteries that can result in heart failure.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HRD</LocID>                         <Text>Hypertensive renal disease</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HRD_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Hypertensive renal disease refers to an increase in systemic blood pressure due to kidney injury or disease.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ANP</LocID>                         <Text>Angina pectoris</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ANP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Angina pectoris refers to chest pain caused by insufficient blood flow to the heart muscle. Angina pectoris is often one of the symptoms of coronary artery disease.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_AMI</LocID>                         <Text>Myocardial infarction</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_AMI_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Acute myocardial infarction, also known as a heart attack, occurs when blood flow to the myocardium (the muscle tissue of the heart) is blocked. The affected muscle tissue can die and the patient is also at high risk of dying.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TAA</LocID>                         <Text>Thoracic aortic aneurysm</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TAA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Thoracic aortic aneurysm refers is a condition where the part of the aorta in the chest cavity is dilated (becomes like a balloon). The aneurysm can rupture and lead to immediate death.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PEM</LocID>                         <Text>Pulmonary embolism</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PEM_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Pulmonary embolism refers to a blockage in one of the pulmonary arteries. The embolism often comes from a dislodged deep venous thrombosis.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ECT</LocID>                         <Text>Endocarditis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ECT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Endocarditis is an infection of the inner lining of the heart. Often the infection arises from bacterial colonization of diseased valves of the heart</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PCT</LocID>                         <Text>Pericarditis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PCT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Pericarditis refers to condition where the thin membrane, or sac, surrounding the heart is inflamed.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_INM</LocID>                         <Text>Myocarditis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_INM_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Myocarditis is an inflammation of the heart's muscle, also known as myocardium, affecting the ability of the heart to pump blood properly and also the heart's electrical system, potentially giving rise to different arrhythmiaes (irregular and abnormal heart rythms).</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CAR</LocID>                         <Text>Cardiac arrest</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CAR_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Cardiac arrest is the sudden loss of the ability of the heart to pump blood. Cardiac arrest is often the result of acute myocardial infarction or sudden malignant arrythmiaes</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CHF</LocID>                         <Text>CHF</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CHF_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Congestive heart failure where the heart loses its ability to pump a sufficient amount of blood into the body.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_STK</LocID>                         <Text>Stroke</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_STK_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Stroke occurs when the blood supply to an area of the brain is interrupted or severely reduced, resulting in the death (necrosis) of brain tissue in the affected area.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ATH</LocID>                         <Text>Atherosclerosis - Carotides</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ATH_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Atherosclerosis is a disease where plaques are built up inside the carotid arteries of the body (the large arteries running from the aorta to the head), hardening and narrowing them, thereby reducing the flow of blood. It could be asymptomatic for decades, symptoms often appear when arteries become more than 50% blocked.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TPB</LocID>                         <Text>Thrombophlebitis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TPB_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Thrombophlebitis is condition where the inflammation of veins result in the formation of a blood clot that blocks one or more veins.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PVT</LocID>                         <Text>Portal vein thrombosis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PVT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Portal vein thrombosis refers to a condition where the portal vein (the large vein from the intestines to the liver) is blocked by blood clot.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PEB</LocID>                         <Text>Pulmonary hypertension</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PEB_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Pulmonary hypertension is hypertension in the arteries from the heart to the lungs. Pulmonary hypertension often happens due to large or many small pulmonary emboli (blood clots in the lungs).</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PAD</LocID>                         <Text>PAD</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PAD_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Peripheral artery disease is caused by a reduced blood flow to the upper or lower limbs due to narrowed arteries, often from artherosclerotic disease.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_MVP</LocID>                         <Text>Mitral valve prolapse</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_MVP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Mitral valve prolapse is a condition where the heart's mitral valve bulges into the left atrium during the contraction of the left ventricle. This is usually following an acute myocardial infarction affecting the attachment of the valve in the left ventricle.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_DCP</LocID>                         <Text>Dilated cardiomyopathy</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_DCP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Dilated cardiomyopathy is a condition where the heart becomes severely enlarged, reducing the ability of the heart to pump, making the heart unable to effectively pump a sufficient amount of blood into the bloodstream.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_GCA</LocID>                         <Text>Giant cells arteritis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_GCA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Giant cells arteritis is an inflammation of the arterial lining, mainly in the temporal arteries on the side of the head.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_BCI</LocID>                         <Text>Cardiac blunt injury</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_BCI_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Cardiac blunt injury is physical trauma to a chest area, resulting in a trauma to the heart.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_FLC</LocID>                         <Text>Flail chest</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_FLC_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Flail chest is a life-threatening condition that occurs when a segment of the rib cage breaks due to trauma and moves independently of the rest of the chest wall/ribs during breathing.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_TCA</LocID>                         <Text>Traumatic cardiac arrest</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_TCA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Traumatic cardiac arrest is a condition where the heart has ceased to beat due to blunt or penetrating trauma, such as a stab wound hitting the hard. It is a surgical emergency which will always result in death without immediate surgical care.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_TAR</LocID>                         <Text>Aortic rupture</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_TAR_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Traumatic aortic rupture is a condition where the aorta, the largest artery in the body, ruptures as a result of aortic disease (aortic aneurysm, aortic dissection) or trauma to the body. The condition is frequently fatal due to the massive bleeding that results from the rupture. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <!-- ===================== -->
            <!-- Diagnoses - Neurology -->
            <!-- ===================== -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TBE</LocID>                         <Text>Tick-borne encephalitis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TBE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Tick-borne encephalitis is a viral tick-borne infectious disease involving brain and central nervous system.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ECS</LocID>                         <Text>Encephalitis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ECS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Encephalitis is an inflammation of the brain, most commonly caused by an autoimmune reaction or viruses.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_RAB</LocID>                         <Text>Rabies</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_RAB_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Rabies is a deadly virus spread by saliva of infected animals. Transmission is often through animal bites.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PMN</LocID>                         <Text>Pneumococcal meningitis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_PMN_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Pneumococcal meningitis is an inflammation of membranes covering the spinal cord and brain due to the pneumococcal infection.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_SMN</LocID>                         <Text>Staphylococcal meningitis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_SMN_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Staphylococcal meningitis is an inflammation of membranes covering the spinal cord and brain due to the staphylococcal infection.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_MIG</LocID>                         <Text>Migraine</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_MIG_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Migraine is a severe, painful headache with or without aura.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_GBS</LocID>                         <Text>Guillain-Barre syndrome</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_GBS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Guillain-Barre syndrome is a serious disease where the immune system attacks its own nervous system.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_NMO</LocID>                         <Text>Neuromyelitis optica</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_NMO_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Neuromyelitis optica is an auto-immune disease where the immune system attacks the eye nerves and the spinal cord. A condition that is often seen because of multiple sclerosis. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_IPD</LocID>                         <Text>CIPD</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_IPD_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Chronic inflammatory demyelinizating polyneuropathy is an immune inflammatory disease affecting peripheral nervous system by destructing the cover sheet that protect and insulate the nerves and fibres.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TTN</LocID>                         <Text>Tetanus</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_TTN_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Tetanus is a serious bacterial disease affecting the nervous system.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_BLP</LocID>                         <Text>Blepharitis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_BLP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Blepharitis is inflammation of the eyelid.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CJN</LocID>                         <Text>Conjunctivitis (bacterial)</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CJN_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Conjunctivitis  known as "Pink eye" is an inflammatory disease of the outermost layer of the white part of the eye.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CAN</LocID>                         <Text>Conjunctivitis (allergic)</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CAN_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Conjunctivitis  known as "Pink eye" is an inflammatory disease of the outermost layer of the white part of the eye.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_GLC</LocID>                         <Text>Open-angle glaucoma</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_GLC_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Glaucoma is a disease that results in damage to the optic nerve, because of high pressure inside the eye .</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CLH</LocID>                         <Text>Cluster headache</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CLH_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Cluster headaches are extremely painful headaches, often with crying and a dripping nose, that only occur on one side of the head.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HRP</LocID>                         <Text>Hypertensive retinopathy</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_HRP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Hypertensive retinopathy is damage to the retina and retina’s blood vessels due to high blood pressure.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_UVE</LocID>                         <Text>Uveitis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_UVE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Uveitis refers to inflammation of the part of the eye called the uvea. The uvea includes the iris and some adjacent structures.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_SCL</LocID>                         <Text>Scleritis</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_SCL_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Scleritis refers to inflammation of the sclera of the eye.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_KRT</LocID>                         <Text>Keratitis - bacterial</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_KRT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Keratitis is an inflammatory disease, mostly caused by bacteria, of the cornea - the clear dome surface of the eye.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CAB</LocID>                         <Text>Corneal abrasion</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CAB_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Corneal abrasion - known also as scratched eye is one of the most common eye injuries, when foreign obstacles scratches the eye and produce discomfort and related symptoms.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ACG</LocID>                         <Text>Angle-closure glaucoma</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_ACG_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Acute angle-closure glaucoma is caused by sudden and rapid increase of the intraocular pressure.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CRV</LocID>                         <Text>CRVO</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>DIA_CRV_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Central retinal vein occlusion is one of the common vascular disorders of the eye's retina.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_CCS</LocID>                         <Text>Concussion</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_CCS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>A concussion is a mild traumatic brain injury resulting in temporary altered mental state and/or loss of function.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_CTS</LocID>                         <Text>Cerebral contusion</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_CTS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Cerebral contusion is a traumatic brain injury usually due to blunt head trauma.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_DAI</LocID>                         <Text>Diffuse axonal injury</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_DAI_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Diffuse axonal injury is one of the most common head traumas, it occurs when the brain shifts too quickly inside the skull.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_TBI</LocID>                         <Text>Traumatic brain injury</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_TBI_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Occurs when an external force injures the brain. It can be caused by accidents or blunt trauma.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_AIH</LocID>                         <Text>Subdural hematoma</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_AIH_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Subdural hematoma is a condition where veins in the subdural space are torn and start to bleed. Blood accumulates in the narrow space which increases the pressure inside the skull cavity. The condition is often fatal if left untreated.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_OBI</LocID>                         <Text>Penetrating trauma - Head</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TRM_OBI_DESCRIPTION</LocID>             <Text>Penetrating head injury is an injury in which the dura mater, the outer layer of the meninges, is breached.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>


        </LocalizedStrings>
    </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
