<Database>
    <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_DE_TUTORIAL">
        
        <LanguageCode>de</LanguageCode>
        <LanguageNameLocalized>Deutsch</LanguageNameLocalized>

        <Contributors>
            <Name>Pythagorion</Name>
        </Contributors>
        
        <LocalizedStrings>
            <!-- ======================== -->
            <!--LEVEL 1 - DIAGNOSE: Flow 1-->
            <!-- ======================== -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_DIAGNOSING_INTRODUCTION</LocID>    <Text>Hey Chef. Danke, dass du wieder da bist, um uns zu helfen. Wir wissen, du hattest deine Gründe für den Ruhestand, aber wir kannst wirklich jemand mit deinem Talent gebrauchen. \nWir wissen, dass du gut darin warst, Kranheiten von Patien zu diagnostizieren.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_WELCOME</LocID>               <Text>Wir haben Probleme mit dem Personal, könntest du uns mit ein paar Patienten helfen?\nOh, Keine Sorge, Ich werde dir zeigen, wie alles hier nun funktioniert.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_ZOOM_IN</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[Lass uns zuerst beobachten, was ab geht. Du kannst mit dem Mausrad <b><i>heran- und herauszoomen</i></b> und Rotieren, indem du die mittlere Maustaste gedrückt hälst.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_WALL_CONFIGURATION</LocID>    <Text><![CDATA[Du siehst außerdem, dass die Wände deine Sicht versperren kannst.<b><i>Verändere</i></b> deinen Blickwinkel, nach deinem Belieben.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_SELECT_PATIENT</LocID>        <Text><![CDATA[Ausgezeichnet, nun <b><i>wähle den Patienten aus</i></b>, der geduldig in dem Arztzimmer auf uns wartet.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_PATIENT_CARD</LocID>          <Text>Das hier ist die Patientenkarte. du beinhaltet alle wichtigen Informationen und du kannst überprüfen, was mit deinen Patienten passiert.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_LAST_SELECTED</LocID>         <Text>Auf der rechten Seite siehst du die Chronik der letzten 6 ausgewählten Charaktere.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_PORTRAIT</LocID>              <Text>Wenn du auf das Portrait eines Charakters klickst, zentriert die Kamera auf diesen.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_PATIENTS_CONTROL</LocID>      <Text>Du kannst entscheiden, wer für deinen Patienten zuständig sein soll. Entweder du lässt dein Personal sich darum kümmern oder du kannst das direkt selber übernehmen. Kümmere dich um diesen Patienten selber.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_NEEDS_PANEL</LocID>           <Text>Der obere Teil der Karte zeigt dir die persönlichen Daten des Patienten und die Abteilungszugehörigkeit. Die Bedürfnis-Tafel auf der rechten Seite zeigt den Zufriedenheitsgrad. Zudem siehst du darunter die Boni und Ticks eines Charakters.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_DIAGNOSES</LocID>             <Text>Die nächste Tafel zeigt alle möglichen Diagnosen, die mit den bekannten Symptomen des Patienten übereinstimmen, sortiert von dem wahrscheinlichsten Treffer zum Unwahrscheinlichsten. Die Auswahl einer Diagnose ist final und kann nicht verändert werden.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_SYMPTOMS</LocID>              <Text>Die Symptome-Tafel zeigt alle enthüllten und verborgenen Symptome. Auf der linken Seite kannst du sehen, welcher Arzt welchen Patienten behandelt.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_EXAMINATIONS</LocID>          <Text><![CDATA[Dies ist die Untersuchungstafel, wo du die Untersuchungen sortieren kannst, um zu enthüllen, welche Symptome die verborgenen sind. Versuche den <b><i>Haut-Injektionstest auszuwählen</i></b>, um ausreichend verborgene Symptome zu enthüllen, so dass nur eine mögliche Diagnose übrig bleibt.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_PATIENT_DIAGNOSED</LocID>     <Text><![CDATA[Du kannst sehen, welche vollendeten Untersuchungen ein Symptom enthüllt haben. Diese werden in Grün hervorgehoben. Fahre nun fort und <b><i>wähle die Diagnose aus, die als Einzige übrig geblieben ist.</i></b>]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_TREATMENTS</LocID>            <Text><![CDATA[Nun hält uns nichts mehr davon ab, den Patienten zu behandeln. Du kannst mit der Maus über das Symbol deiner ausgewählten Diagnose fahren, um einen Hinweis zu sehen, welcher die richtige Therapie vorschlägt. Fahre fort und <b><i>wähle die Therapie.</i></b>]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_GOOD_JOB</LocID>              <Text>Gut gemacht, du hast deinen ersten Patienten behandelt. Abhängig von der ausgewählten Therapie, wird dein Patient geheilt werden oder später mit neuen Symptomen zurückkehren.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_CONTINUE</LocID>              <Text>Kümmern wir uns um den nächsten Patienten.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <!-- ======================== -->
            <!--LEVEL 1 - DIAGNOSE: Flow 2-->
            <!-- ======================== -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_OPEN_CARD</LocID>             <Text><![CDATA[Hier ist unser nächster Patient. <b><i>Klicke auf den Patient, welcher im Arztzimmer sitzt.</i></b>]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_COMPLICATED_CASE</LocID>      <Text>Wahrscheinlich hast du vorhin gemerkt, dass manche Untersuchen nicht verfügbar waren (grau gefärbt). Diese benötigen spezielle Räume oder Ausrüstung.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_MISSING_STUFF</LocID>         <Text>Wenn du mit der Maus über ein ausgegrautes Symbol fährst, zeigt dir ein Hinweis, was noch fehlt. In diesem Fall fehlt uns sowohl der Raum, als auch ein Technologe, welcher das Röntgengerät bedient.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_TOOLTIP</LocID>               <Text>Während des Spiels sind ständig Hinweise verfügbar, die zusätzliche Informationen zu jedem Symbol in jeder Kategorie enthalten.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_FIX_MISSING_STUFF</LocID>     <Text>Lass uns fürs Erste die Klinik reparieren.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <!-- ======================== -->
            <!--LEVEL 1 - DIAGNOSE: Flow 3-->
            <!-- ======================== -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_FIXED</LocID>                 <Text><![CDATA[Alles sollte nun in Ordnung sein und wenn du <b><i>die Patientenkarte erneut öffnest, kannst du die nun verfügbare Untersuchung auswählen.</i></b>]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_BOOKMARK</LocID>              <Text>Wenn du in der Dauerschleife bleiben willst, musst du den Patienten unter deiner Aufsicht halten oder ihn überwachen. Dasselbe Symbol The same icon wechselt zwischen allen Modi.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_BOOKMARKED</LocID>            <Text>Im Augenblick steht der Patient unter deiner Aufsicht, genau wie wir es haben wollen.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_CARD_OPTIONS</LocID>          <Text>Die Karte kann geschlossen werden, indem du das X in der oberen rechten Ecke drückst. Vergiss nicht: Du kannst jederzeit die letzten paar Patienten über die Liste auf der rechten Seite betrachten.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_TIME_MANIPULATION</LocID>     <Text><![CDATA[Diese Untersuchung wird ein bisschen Zeit in Anspruch nehmen. Du kannst <b><i>die Geschwindigkeit der Zeit erhöhen,</i></b> indem du die Bedienelemente in der Mitte des Hauptfensters verwendest.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_WAITING_FOR_RESULTS</LocID>   <Text>Sehen wir uns an, was mit unserem Patient geschieht.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_STAT_LAB_RESULTS</LocID>      <Text>Die PopUp-Benachrichtigung informiert dich darüber, dass das Röntgen ein Symptom offenbart hat.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_POP_UP</LocID>                <Text>Du kannst die Art und Weise, wie du Benachrichtigungen erhalten möchten, ändern, indem du es zu 'Pop-Up' oder 'Protokoll' wechselst.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_POP_UP_CLOSE</LocID>          <Text>Mit einem Klick auf OK kannst du die Benachrichtigung schließen.</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_LOG</LocID>                   <Text>Du kannst die Benachrichtigungen über das Protokollfenster unten rechts im Bildschirm wieder öffnen.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_FINAL_DIAGNOSE</LocID>        <Text>Die letzte Röntgenuntersuchung ergab ein letztes verstecktes Symptom, das einzigartig für die Krankheit des Patienten ist. Wenn die Diagnose nicht eindeutig gewesen wäre, würde dies sie nun mit einer 100%igen Wahrscheinlichkeit bestätigen.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_PRIORITIES</LocID>            <Text>Normalerweise sind laufende Tests (Radiologie, STAT-Labore) der sicherste Weg, um eine Diagnose zu bestätigen, aber sie dauern auch viel Zeit. Du kannst die Behandlung des Patienten selbst beenden oder dem Arzt überlassen.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_OBJECTIVES</LocID>            <Text><![CDATA[Jetzt, wo wir die Grundlagen geklärt haben, ist es an der Zeit, diese Klinik in Betrieb zu nehmen. <b><i>Behandle von 5 Patienten.</i></b>]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_TUTORIAL_1_FINISHED</LocID>   <Text><![CDATA[Perfekt, du hast es geschafft. Vielen Dank für deine Hilfe! Wir kannst von hier aus übernehmen. Ich denke, du wirst woanders gebraucht. <b><i>Klicke auf Weiter, um fortzufahren.</i></b>]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <!-- ======================== -->
            <!--LEVEL 2 - BUILDING: Flow 1-->
            <!-- ======================== -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_BUILDING_INTRODUCTION</LocID>              <Text>Hey Chef. Uns ist wieder eingefallen, dass du nicht nur an Diagnosen beteiligt warst, sondern auch am Bau von Kliniken.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HELLO</LocID>                         <Text>Also, willkommen in dieser schönen Immobilie, die wir kürzlich erworben haben! Wir erklären dir nochmal, wie du deine eigene Klinik bauen und einrichten kannst und welche Möglichkeiten es gibt.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_BUILDING_MODE</LocID>                 <Text><![CDATA[In Ordnung, lasst uns zuerst eine schöne kleine Klinik bauen! Wechseln wir in den Baumodus. Du kannst <b><i>den Button in der oberen linken Ecke nutzen</i></b> oder einfach die F6-Taste drücken.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_FOUNDATIONS</LocID>                   <Text><![CDATA[Der erste wichtige Schritt ist die Erschaffung eines Fundaments. Das Fundamententool ist bereits ausgewählt - <b>decke einen Bereich ab, der groß genug ist, um mindestens 3 Räume zu beherbergen.<i></i></b> (z.B. 20x20 Fliesen).]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_CATEGORIES</LocID>                    <Text>Exzellent! Hier ist nun eine kurze Zusammenfassung dessen, was es zu bauen gibt. Es gibt 5 Hauptkategorien: Fundamente, Konstruktionen, Türen und Fenster, Objekte und Fertigteilhäuser.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_SUB_CATEGORIES</LocID>                <Text>Jede Kategorie ist in Unterkategorien unterteilt. Vergiss nicht, dass es für jede Kategorie und jeden Artikel einen Hinweis mit weiteren Informationen gibt!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_LOGISTICS</LocID>                     <Text><![CDATA[Jetzt, da wir einen Platz zum Bauen haben, müssen wir unseren Grundriss gestalten. Die Grundversorgung eines jeden Krankenhauses ist eine Notaufnahme. <b>Wähle den Verwaltungsmodus aus,<i></i></b> um zu sehen, welche Räume wir definitiv brauchen, um die Notaufnahme betriebsbereit zu machen.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_LOGISTICS_ROOMS</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[Die Liste ist unterteilt in obligatorische und optionale Räume. <b><i>Lass uns einen von jedem platzieren: ein Arztbüro, ein Wartezimmer und eine Toilette.</i></b> Diese werden für eine funktionierende Klinik benötigt.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_BUILD_WALLS</LocID>                   <Text><![CDATA[Prima! Nun, wo der Grundriss fertig ist: <b><i>Lass uns ein paar Mauern bauen.</i>Du findest sie im Baumodus unter der Rubrik 'Konstruktionen'.</b>. ]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_WALLS_INFO</LocID>                    <Text>Großartig! Manchmal sind Wände nicht erforderlich, damit die Räume funktionieren, aber einige Objekte müssen an einer Wand aufgehängt werden.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_WALLS_ADDITIONAL_INFO</LocID>         <Text>Du kannst auch die Wandfarbe wählen und ob du Wände in einer Linie oder in einem Rechteckmuster baust. Die verschiedenen Optionen und Werkzeuge sind immer am unteren Rand des Bau-Fensters dargestellt.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_FLOOR_INFO</LocID>                    <Text><![CDATA[Du kannst auch verschiedene Arten von Böden, Türen und Fenstern bauen. Vergiss nicht, Türen zu platzieren, damit deine Räume und das Gebäude selbst zugänglich sind. Wenn du mit deinem Setup zufrieden bist, <b><i>klicke auf Weiter</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_SELECT_ROOM</LocID>                   <Text><![CDATA[Konzentrieren wir uns darauf, die Räume jetzt einzurichten. <b><i>Klicke einfach auf den Boden</i></b> in einem der Räume.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_EQUIPMENT_INFO</LocID>                <Text>Das Fenster zeigt Möbel und Ausstattungen, die entweder obligatorisch (orange) oder empfohlen (gelb) für den Raum sind. Obligatorische Angaben zeigen auch Alternativen auf. Zum Beispiel alle Geräteschränke. Aber du brauchst nur einen. Du kannst Objekte drehen, indem du R oder die mittlere Maustaste drückst.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_EQUIPMENT_ADDITIONAL_INFO</LocID>     <Text>Die rechte Maustaste bricht die aktuelle Auswahl ab. Einige Objekte benötigen zusätzliche Ausrüstung, um zu funktionieren. Wenn das Objekt in der Szene blau getönt ist, kannst du mit der Maus darüber (oder den Boden darunter) fahren und sehen, welche andere Ausrüstung benötigt wird. Es wird im Ausrüstungsfenster blau angezeigt.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_EQUIPMENT_OBJECTIVE</LocID>           <Text><![CDATA[<b><i>Statte nun deine Räume aus.</i></b>\nBeim Platzieren von Objekten zeigen Pfeile auf dem Boden an, aus welcher Richtung man auf sie zugreifen können muss.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_OPTIONAL_EQUIPMENT</LocID>            <Text>Die optionale Ausstattung beinhaltet in der Regel Dekorationen oder Objekte, die im gegebenen Raum keinen bestimmten Zweck erfüllen, sondern nur die Umgebung verbessern.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_INGAME_TUTORIAL</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[Jetzt brauchen wir nur noch einen Arzt für eine funktionierende Klinik. Wir werden einen mit Hilfe unseres In-Game-Tutorials einstellen - diese sind auch im Sandbox-Modus verfügbar.<b><i>Wähle In-Game-Tutorials aus</i></b>.]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_INGAME_TUTORIAL_HIRING</LocID>        <Text><![CDATA[<b><i>Wähle 'Einstellen' aus</i></b> und folge den Anweisungen,<b><i> um einen Arzt für die Notaufnahme einzustellen.</i></b>]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_SELECT_RADIOLOGY</LocID>              <Text><![CDATA[Wenn du mehrere Abteilungen hast, kannst du zwischen ihnen wechseln, indem du die Symbole in dem Hauptfenster benutzt.<b><i> Wähle Radiologieabteilung aus und öffne den Verwaltungsmodus erneut.</i></b>.]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_BUILD_RADIOLOGY</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[Überprüfe, welche Räume du für eine funktionierende Radiologie brauchst. <b><i>Baue sie, rüste sie aus und besetze sie mit Personal.</i></b> Alle roten Warnungen müssen erledigt werden, um eine funktionierende Abteilung zu haben. Überprüfe, welche Räume du für eine funktionierende Radiologie brauchst.]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_INGAME_HIRE_LAB_SPECIALIST</LocID>    <Text><![CDATA[Der letzte Schritt auf dem Weg zu einer funktionierenden Radiologie ist, <b><i>einen Technologen für den Röntgenraum einzustellen.</i></b> Befolge die gleichen Schritte wie bei der Einstellung eines Arztes.]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_TREAT_PATIENTS</LocID>                <Text><![CDATA[Beende es nun: <b><i>Behandle 8 Patienten.</i></b>]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_PREFABS_CATEGORY</LocID>              <Text><![CDATA[Bevor wir fertig sind, werfen wir einen Blick auf die letzte Kategorie und eine tolle Zeitersparnis - Fertigteilhäuser. <b><i>Wähle die Fertigteilhäuser-Kategorie im Baumodus aus.</i></b> ]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_PREFAB_CATEGORY_SELECTED</LocID>      <Text><![CDATA[Nun kannst du die verschiedenen Räume nach Abteilungen gegliedert sehen. Wähle einen der vorgefertigten Bereiche aus und platziere ihn in einem ungenutzten Bereich in deiner Klinik.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_PREFAB_PLACED</LocID>                 <Text>Du hast jetzt einen voll ausgestatteten Raum platziert - er wird auch automatisch in den Grundriss eingefügt. Du kannst ihn natürlich genau an deine Bedürfnisse anpassen.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_TUTORIAL_2_FINISHED</LocID>           <Text>Gut gemacht! Es ist wie Fahrradfahren, nicht wahr?</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <!-- ============================================== -->
            <!--LEVEL 3 - MANAGEMENT AND HOSPITALIZATION: Flow 1-->
            <!-- ============================================== -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_MANAGEMENT_INTRODUCTION</LocID>                    <Text>Hi boss, with diagnosing and building out of the way, we know that you have one more talent, that also might need little refreshment.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_WELCOME_MANAGEMENT</LocID>                    <Text>Let's take a closer look at hospital management.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_DEPARTMENT_CARD_OPEN</LocID>                  <Text><![CDATA[We can start with department management. Go ahead and <b><i>switch to department management mode</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_DEPARTMENT_CARD_INFO</LocID>                  <Text>This mode gives you all the information about your selected department, assigned staff and rooms. It also acts as a checklist for making the department work.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_CHIEF_INFO</LocID>                            <Text>You can choose who will be the chief doctor. Be careful with this selection, it can have a big effect on the overall productivity of your employees.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_CERTAINTY</LocID>                             <Text>"Certainty" level is an important setting for diagnostics. It determines how careful the doctors are when selecting a final diagnosis and how carefully they look for hidden symptoms.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HIRING</LocID>                                <Text><![CDATA[Let's have a look at your hiring options. Click on the <b><i>hiring button</i></b> in your desired department's card.]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HIRING_SELECTED</LocID>                       <Text>There are four staff categories - doctors, nurses, technologists and janitors. You can see their experience levels, skills and their requested salary. Also the character perks can make a big difference and are often hidden.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HIRING_OPTIONS</LocID>                        <Text>The selection is bound to the selected department, so the employees only have matching specializations.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HIRING_AGENCY</LocID>                         <Text>If you're not happy with the candidates, a hiring agency will be happy to provide you with a new list or uncover hidden perks for a fee.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HIRE_EMPLOYEE_INFO</LocID>                    <Text>To hire an employee, click on their portrait and drop them into a room. The employee will be automatically assigned to the nearest workplace. You can also assign the workplace from the employee card.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HIRE_EMPLOYEE_TASK</LocID>                    <Text><![CDATA[Hire a <b><i>doctor for emergency department</i></b> and <b><i>a technologist for radiology department</i></b>.\n\nTip: You can switch the department at the bottom left of the main panel.]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_LOGISTICS_SELECT</LocID>                      <Text><![CDATA[Now you can check their assigned workspaces. <b><i>Select management mode</i></b>.]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_WORKSPACES</LocID>                            <Text>Workspaces consist of a desk, chair and a pc as you've probably seen when building different rooms. And you can see they are now occupied (on your selected department). You can also click on an empty workspace and hire an employee that way.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_EMPLOYEE_CARD</LocID>                         <Text><![CDATA[Let's have a closer look at your staff. <b><i>Open any of your employee's card</i></b>.]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_EMPLOYEE_CARD_LEVELS</LocID>                  <Text>Every employee has a few different statistics: their level, skills and specializations. For technologists and nurses there are three experience levels, for doctors five. Different specializations get available as the employees level up.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_EMPLOYEE_CARD_SKILLS</LocID>                  <Text>Skills are fixed for each type of personnel, but get improved by being used. You can learn more about individual skills in tooltips.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_EMPLOYEE_CARD_SPECIALIZATIONS</LocID>         <Text>Specializations give the opportunity to work at certain departments or rooms and allow the employee to perform specific examinations or treatments.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_EMPLOYEE_CARD_SECOND_SPECIALIZATION</LocID>   <Text>Doctors can have one or two specializations. The first one allows basic work at a certain deparment and is available for all residents (level 2), the second one is usually related to surgery or diagnostics and available for fellows (level 4).</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_EMPLOYEE_CARD_ROLES</LocID>                   <Text>Employee roles give you the option to control what tasks each employee is allowed to preform. This way you can make sure that you have staff available when they are really needed, for example for surgery.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_NIGHT_SHIFT</LocID>                           <Text><![CDATA[To be able to take care of hospitalized patients 24/7, the hospital needs staff assigned to both day shift and night shift. <b><i>Click on “night shift” button</i></b>]]>.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_DEPARTMENTS</LocID>                           <Text><![CDATA[Let's move to mamagement tools for the whole hospital. First, let's have a look at departments. <b><i>Open the department section</i></b> of the hospital management card.]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_DEPARTMENTS_OPENED</LocID>                    <Text>Here's a list of all of active departments. You can close them down from here.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_INSURANCE_COMPANY</LocID>                     <Text><![CDATA[Insurance companies are your most important partners because they control both what patients come to the hospital and how much they pay. <b><i>Open the insurance section</i></b> of the hospital management card.]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_INSURANCE_COMPANY_OPENED</LocID>              <Text>Insurance companies have their own requirements, but when you pass these, it's up to you which insurance companies you contract and accept patients from.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_AMBULANCE</LocID>                             <Text><![CDATA[Now we will take a look at ambulances. <b><i>Open the ambulance section</i></b> of the hospital management card.]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_AMBULANCE_OPENED</LocID>                      <Text>The panel shows you the status of all your ambulances.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_BUDGET</LocID>                                <Text><![CDATA[Next up: finance. <b><i>Open the budget section</i></b> of the hospital management card.]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_BUDGET_OPENED</LocID>                         <Text>Here's a breakdown of your income and expenses for each department. You can also take a loan from a local bank if you are short on cash.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_STATISTICS</LocID>                            <Text><![CDATA[And last but not least, statistics. <b><i>Open the statistics section</i></b> of the hospital management card.]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_STATISTICS_OPENED</LocID>                     <Text>The statistics give you some insight into how well is your hospital doing and what the trends have been.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <!-- Hospitalization -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_DEPARTMENT_HOSPITALIZATION_INFO</LocID>       <Text>Now onto the fun part. Our hospital needs a functional hospitalization at general surgery department.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_BUILD_DEPARTMENT_HOSPITALIZATION</LocID>      <Text><![CDATA[Switch to department management and select general surgery department, check what rooms you need and <b><i>build them</i></b>. Then <b><i>hire necessary staff</i></b>. All of the red warning signs must be dealt with to get hospitalization to work.]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_AMBULANCE_PATIENT</LocID>                     <Text><![CDATA[Now that we have working hospitalization, the ambulance will bring us our first patient. <b><i>This should be only a minute!</i></b>]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_AMBULANCE_PATIENT_SELECT</LocID>              <Text><![CDATA[Let's pause the game so you can select the patient easily and <b><i>take the patient under your care</i></b>.]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HOSPITAL_OVERVIEW</LocID>                     <Text><![CDATA[Now let's us follow the patient though our hospitalization process. This can start at the emergency department with <i>observation</i> or <i>trauma hospitalization</i>.]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HOSPITAL_OBSERVATION</LocID>                  <Text>Patients get admitted for observation when there is no clear diagnosis and the patient could have one or more dangerous symptoms. Once the diagnosis is clear, the patient gets treated and sent home or hospitalized at a specialized department.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HOSPITAL_OBSERVATION_INFO</LocID>             <Text>When the patient goes to an observation room, following examinations will be done by the on-call room staff and your doctor in the doctor's office at the clinic will take another case.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HOSPITAL_TRAUMA_CENTER_OVERVIEW</LocID>       <Text>Trauma center is an essential unit for handling different types of traumas and accidents and most critical cases that your ambulances bring to the hospital arrive here.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HOSPITAL_TRAUMA_CENTER_INFO</LocID>           <Text>Trauma center works the same way as the observation room. As long as the diagnosis is not clear, the patient will be examined here.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HOSPITAL_TRAUMA_CENTER_TASK</LocID>           <Text><![CDATA[Now let's go back to our patient on their way to the trauma center. Try to find out what is wrong and <b><i>reach a clear diagnosis</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_DEPARTMENT_HOSPITALIZATION</LocID>            <Text>With a clear diagnosis the patients get hospitalized at specialized departments. Every department has two types of inpatient rooms, regular or HDU hospitalization.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_NORMAL_HOSPITALIZATION</LocID>                <Text>Regular ward is suitable for patients without any risk of life threatening conditions.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HIGH_HOSPITALIZATION</LocID>                  <Text>High dependency unit is suitable for patients in risk of collapse or life threatening conditions. They are generally equipped with life monitors to keep an eye on the vital functions of their patients.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_ICU_HOSPITALIZATION</LocID>                   <Text>If patients collapse, they can be sent to ICU to be connected to life support and to get continuous care. Intensive care unit is not only a hospitalization type, but also a standalone department.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_CHANGE_DEPARTMENT</LocID>                     <Text><![CDATA[So, what's the next step for our patient? Let's <b><i>switch the department</i></b>. Check the tooltip on the diagnosis to see which department is capable of treating it.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_CHANGE_DEPARTMENT_WAIT</LocID>                <Text><![CDATA[Let's <b><i>wait</i></b> for our patient to be transferred to their room. The room was chosen based on the severity of patient's symptoms.\nTip: You can follow the patient by clicking the hidden cross over the bottom left corner of their portrait.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_DOCTORS_ROUNDS</LocID>                        <Text>Hospitals work around the clock and there are a few important times in the daily schedule. Doctor's rounds happen every morning, when the doctors visit their patients and order additional examinations.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_NURSES_CHECKUPS</LocID>                       <Text>Nurses check the patients regularly, more often at HDU and ICU. They can notice dangerous symptoms and notify the doctors so the patients get examined.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_NURSES_MEDICINE_LUNCH</LocID>                 <Text>Nurses also deliver meals and medicine in various forms, as prescribed.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_DEATH</LocID>                                 <Text>...and when everything goes horribly wrong? Well, sometimes that happens even if you do everything right and patients will die.\nNote: death can be turned off in options, the patients will be transferred away instead.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_TREAT_AMBULACE_PATIENT</LocID>                <Text><![CDATA[Now it's time to treat our patient. <b><i>Suppress all high hazard symptoms</i></b>, notice some icons are pulsing. Patient might collapse and die if you don't prescribe the correct treatments.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_TREAT_AMBULACE_PATIENT_SENT_AWAY</LocID>      <Text>Unfortunately patient collapsed and without functional ICU must be transported away. Make sure you have enough staff available and correct roles assigned because sometimes, time is of the essence.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_TREAT_AMBULACE_PATIENT_DEAD</LocID>           <Text>Unfortunately you were not able to save this patient. Make sure you have enough staff available and correct roles assigned because sometimes, time is of the essence.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_TREAT_AMBULACE_PATIENTS</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[We have couple more patients coming into the hospital <b><i>Suppress their high hazard symptoms</i></b> to save them from danger.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_TREAT_AMBULACE_PATIENTS_ONE_DEAD</LocID>      <Text>Unfortunately you were not able to save one of your patients. Make sure you have enough staff available and correct roles assigned because sometimes, time is of the essence.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_TREAT_AMBULACE_PATIENTS_ONE_SENT_AWAY</LocID> <Text>Unfortunately one of your patients collapsed and without functional ICU must be transported away. Make sure you have enough staff available and correct roles assigned because sometimes, time is of the essence.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HOSPITALIZATION_END</LocID>                   <Text>Hopefully we have covered all the important parts of hospital management and hospitalization. And now we can focus on why we requested your help. Please meet us in our next hospital.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <!-- ======= -->
            <!--BENCHMARK-->
            <!-- ======= -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>LEVEL_BENCHMARK</LocID>                             <Text>Benchmark</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_BENCHMARK</LocID>                     <Text>Benchmark wird ausgeführt. Es wird nur eine Sekunde dauern!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_BENCHMARK_DONE</LocID>                <Text>Benchmark ist erledigt! Bitte mache einen Screenshot bevor du weiter klickst.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

           
            <!-- ========= -->
            <!--CAMPAIGN 01-->
            <!-- ========= -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_01_WELCOME</LocID>                         <Text>Hi boss, how was the refreshment course? You did take it right? We'll need all of your skills if we want to challenge MeDevilCare company. We know that you used to work for MeDevilCare and you helped them to become the best.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_01_HELP</LocID>                            <Text>But their greediness is what you made you leave. And like you, we want to give people the best care possible. And with your help we just might be able to do it.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_01_INTRODUCTION</LocID>                    <Text>That is why we bought this hospital. It used to belong to MeDevilCare, but it was build very fast without consideration about layout and personnel that is why it is very inefficient and loosing money. The main reason they sold it. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_01_TASK</LocID>                            <Text>To be able to take care of our patents we need to make this hospital efficient. See what you can improve and how many patients we can cure now.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_01_TREATED_FIRST_PATIENTS</LocID>          <Text>This is very good start, but now we need to focus on making some profit.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_01_PROFIT_ONE_DONE</LocID>                 <Text>Good job. Making this hospital profitable is drawing more patients that needs your help. Keep it up.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_01_TREATED_SECOND_PATIENTS</LocID>         <Text>It's going very well. Try to keep steady profit now. It can be used on expansion of the hospital.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_01_PROFIT_TWO_DONE</LocID>                 <Text>Fantastic, even more patients are coming to the hospital now. See how much you can cure.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_01_TREATED_PATIENTS_DONE</LocID>           <Text>We knew, we could count on you boss. You made this hospital efficient and thanks to you more patients can be taken care of.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_01_NEW_HOSPITAL</LocID>                    <Text>Unfortunately our work is far from finished. And we need your help in another hospital. We'll meet you there.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <!-- ========= -->
            <!--CAMPAIGN 02-->
            <!-- ========= -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_02_WELCOME</LocID>                         <Text>Hi boss, we are in a pickle in this hospital. Our managers took a huge loan from the bank and ran with all the money.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_02_ROGUE_MANAGER</LocID>                   <Text>We suspect that he was working for MeDevilCare, they just don't want us to succeed. And here, they just might.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_02_BANK_LOANS</LocID>                      <Text>Because if we won't be able to return the money to the bank, we will have to close this hospital. So we need you to do what you do best and help us fix this situation.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_02_BANK_LAST_LOAN</LocID>                  <Text>Since you are new here, the bank will let you borrow money some more money, but we suspect that it is in our best interest to borrow only if really needed.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_02_EVENTS</LocID>                          <Text>Great way how to boost our money income and prestige is to successfully complete events in a row. But be careful because failing can have the opposite outcome. Do them when your hospital is really ready.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_02_TASK</LocID>                            <Text>Now go and keep an eye on the bank and return money as often as possible because you can lower the interest this way.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_02_TASK_DONE</LocID>                       <Text>Good job, you were able to return all the money back to the bank and restored our hospital and company reputation.</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_02_TASK_DONE_IN_TIME</LocID>               <Text>Amazing job, you were able to return all the money back to the bank and restored our hospital and company reputation. And you did it in record time.</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_02_NEW_HOSPITAL</LocID>                    <Text>Now the time has come for our biggest challenge. When you are ready meet us in our next hospital.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <!-- ========= -->
            <!--CAMPAIGN 03-->
            <!-- ========= -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_03_WELCOME</LocID>                         <Text>Hi boss, this is our most functional hospital we have. Yes some things need to improve as always. We also need to show that our medical company can really give patients more then MeDevilCare. And we just found a way.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_03_STATE_SUPPORT</LocID>                   <Text>State is looking to invest into the best medical company around. And with that grand and your skills we can really make a difference.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_03_MONEY_OBJECTIVE</LocID>                 <Text>You have shown that you can run an efficient hospital that can earn money. And that is one way to be considered for the grant. To earn big amount of money over a period of time. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_03_PRESTIGE_OBJECTIVE</LocID>              <Text>The other is much harder but also more rewarding and that is keeping a prestige up over a period of time. That means keeping patients and staff happy, even if that means sacrificing money sometimes.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_03_EVENTS_BOOST</LocID>                    <Text>As before you can use events as a way to boost your prestige and money income.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_03_TASK</LocID>                            <Text>How you choose to approach this challenge is up to you. We wish you good luck and may the best win.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_03_PRESTIGE_OBJECTIVE_DONE</LocID>         <Text>Congratulations, you have done it. Our company was chosen for the grant thanks to you. And you showed us that you care about your hospital, staff and patients. Keep up the good work.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_03_MONEY_OBJECTIVE_DONE</LocID>            <Text>Congratulations, you have done it. Our company was chosen for the grant thanks to you. You may have chosen the way we did not expect, but we can't argue with the result. Try to keep up the good work.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>CAMPAIGN_03_SECRET_OBJECTIVE</LocID>                <Text>Unbelievable, you have managed to meet both conditions. You really are the best. Congratulations, you have won.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>


            <!-- ============== -->
            <!--INGAME TUTORIALS-->
            <!-- ============== -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_BUILDING</LocID>                    <Text>Building foundations</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_BUILDING_MODE</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[Select <b><i>building mode</i></b>.\n\nTip: mostly useful width of rooms is 6 tiles and for corridors 4 tiles, so recommended width of the building is 16 tiles.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_BUILDING_FOUNDATION_TOOLS</LocID>   <Text><![CDATA[Go to the <b><i>foundation tools</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_BUILDING_FOUDATIONS</LocID>         <Text><![CDATA[Click on <b><i>building foundations</i></b> icon and drag mouse over the required area.\n\nTip: foundations can be removed only by the dynamite tool.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_BUILDING_CONSTRUCTION_TOOLS</LocID> <Text><![CDATA[Go to <b><i>construction tools</i></b>.]]></Text>   </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_BUILDING_WALLS</LocID>              <Text><![CDATA[Click on <b><i>walls</i></b>.\n\nTip: at the very bottom of the panel are other tools for wall placing or removing.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_BUILDING_MATERIAL</LocID>           <Text><![CDATA[Select your desired <b><i>material</i></b> and drag to create walls or replace their materials.\n\nTip: at the bottom of the panel you can change color of most of the patterns.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_BUILDING_WINDOORS</LocID>           <Text><![CDATA[Click on <b><i>doors and windows</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_BUILDING_WINDOORS_PLACE</LocID>     <Text><![CDATA[Place your <b><i>doors and windows</i></b>.\n\nTip: at the bottom of the panel you can change colors.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_LAYOUT</LocID>                      <Text>Building layout</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_LAYOUT_MANAGEMENT_MODE</LocID>      <Text><![CDATA[Select <b><i>management mode</i></b>.\n\nTip: at the very bottom of the panel there are tools for changing access to your rooms.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_LAYOUT_PLACEMENT</LocID>            <Text><![CDATA[In the clinic or hospital parts click on required <b><i>room</i></b> and drag it into your building.\n\nTip: don't forget to place walls and doors for your new rooms.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_EQUIPMENT</LocID>                   <Text>Room equipment</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_EQUIPMENT_BUILDING_MODE</LocID>     <Text><![CDATA[Select <b><i>building mode</i></b> and right click to cancel the current tool selection.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_EQUIPMENT_ROOM_SELECT</LocID>       <Text><![CDATA[On the floors you can see white icons of your <b><i>rooms</i></b>. Choose one and click\n\nTip: texts in the corners of rooms will tell you what is missing.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_EQUIPMENT_PANEL</LocID>             <Text><![CDATA[Equipment panel shows you all mandatory (orange), recommended (yellow), and optional <b><i>objects</i></b>.\n\nTip: hover mouse around blue objects in room, what's missing will get highlighted in the building panel.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_EQUIPMENT_DECORATIONS</LocID>       <Text><![CDATA[Click on <b><i>decorations</i></b>. Here you can find decorative objects to place to your rooms.\n\nTip: decorative objects can improve the mood of characters in the room.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_EQUIPMENT_DECALS</LocID>            <Text><![CDATA[Click on <b><i>decals</i></b>. Here you can select and use wall decals.\n\nTip: at the bottom of the panel you can change color of the decals.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_HIRING</LocID>                      <Text>Hiring new staff</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_HIRING_MANAGEMENT_MODE</LocID>      <Text><![CDATA[Select <b><i>management mode</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_HIRING_BUTTON</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[Click on the new <b><i>staff</i></b> button.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_HIRING_PROFESSION</LocID>           <Text><![CDATA[Choose what <b><i>profession</i></b> you need.\n\nTip: to know required specialization, hover the mouse over the staff on management panel a read the tooltip.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_HIRING_SHIFTS</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[Choose day or night <b><i>shift</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_HIRING_SELECTION</LocID>            <Text><![CDATA[Select required <b><i>character</i></b> and place them into the room where you want them to work.\n\nTip: after placement the character will automatically find the nearest workspace.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_AMBULANCE</LocID>                   <Text>Ambulance</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_AMBULANCE_BUILDING_MODE</LocID>     <Text><![CDATA[Select <b><i>building mode</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_AMBULANCE_CONSTRUCTION_TOOLS</LocID><Text><![CDATA[Go to <b><i>construction tools</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_AMBULANCE_CLICK</LocID>             <Text><![CDATA[Click on <b><i>ambulance</i></b> and select color.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_AMBULANCE_PLACE</LocID>             <Text><![CDATA[Place your ambulance on <b><i>parking lot.</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_AMBULANCE_PANEL</LocID>             <Text><![CDATA[Open the <b><i>ambulance panel</i></b>. Here you can control number of maximum patients, brought by ambulances.\n\nTip: number of patients also depends on the insurance company setup.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
           
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_ELEVATORS</LocID>                   <Text>Elevators</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_ELEVATORS_BUILDING_MODE</LocID>     <Text><![CDATA[Select <b><i>building mode</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_ELEVATORS_CONSTRUCTION_TOOLS</LocID><Text><![CDATA[Go to <b><i>construction tools</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_ELEVATORS_PLACE</LocID>             <Text><![CDATA[Click on <b><i>elevator</i></b> and place it to your building.\n\nTip: elevator goes through all floors.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_ELEVATORS_REMOVE</LocID>            <Text><![CDATA[Elevator <b><i>remove</i></b> works the same way through all floors.\n\nTip: if you want disable elevator for certain floor, jsut remove the door.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_PREFABS</LocID>                     <Text>Prefabs</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_PREFABS_BUILDING_MODE</LocID>       <Text><![CDATA[Select <b><i>building mode</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_PREFABS_CATEGORY</LocID>            <Text><![CDATA[Go to <b><i>prefabs</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_PREFABS_PLACE</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[Select <b><i>department</i></b>, choose needed <b><i>room</i></b> and place it into the building.\n\nTip: you can rotate room by using "R".]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_PREFABS_COPY</LocID>                <Text><![CDATA[If you want copy room that's already built, click on <b><i>copy/crate prefab</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_PREFABS_COPY_SELECT</LocID>         <Text><![CDATA[<b><i>Drag and drop</i></b> area you want to copy and place it elsewhere. Or save it by <b><i>save prefab</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_PREFABS_SAVED</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[Your created prefabs can be found in category <b><i>saved prefabs</i></b>.\n\nTip: for <b><i>deleting</i></b> saved prefabs, select the prefab and than click on the delete on the tool panel.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
           
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_FINANCE</LocID>                     <Text>Finance</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_FINANCE_PANEL</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[Click on <b><i>finance panel</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_FINANCE_PANEL_INFO</LocID>          <Text><![CDATA[Here you can see finance <b><i>overview</i></b> for all departments and your hospital.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_FINANCE_BANK</LocID>                <Text><![CDATA[You can also borrow money from bank. Click on arrows to <b><i>borrow or repay</i></b>.\n\nTip: loan interest is paid every day.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_FINANCE_OVERVIEW</LocID>            <Text><![CDATA[Overview <b><i>history</i></b> can be found by listing with arrows at the bottom of the panel.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_TABLES</LocID>                      <Text>Character tables</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_TABLES_MANAGEMENT_MODE</LocID>      <Text><![CDATA[Select <b><i>management mode</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_TABLES_OPEN</LocID>                 <Text><![CDATA[In the clinic side, click on the button of <b><i>patients or staff</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_TABLES_FILTER</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[You can <b><i>filter</i></b> the content by using buttons at the left upper corner..]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_CERTAINTY</LocID>                   <Text>Certainty</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_CERTAINTY_MANAGEMENT_MODE</LocID>   <Text><![CDATA[Select <b><i>management mode</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_CERTAINTY_CHANGE_LEVEL</LocID>      <Text><![CDATA[Click on the <b><i>certainty</i></b> to choose level.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_CERTAINTY_LOW</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[<b><i>Low</i></b> means doctors skips some examinations and chooses diagnoses by percentage level. Diagnosing is much faster.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_CERTAINTY_MEDIUM</LocID>            <Text><![CDATA[<b><i>Medium</i></b> means doctors are more consistent in diagnosing, probability of wrong diagnose is lower, but it takes more time.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_CERTAINTY_HIGH</LocID>              <Text><![CDATA[<b><i>High</i></b>, doctors are trying to find as much symptoms as possible, diagnosing is very slow, but with no chance of wrong diagnose.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_CLOSE_DEP</LocID>                   <Text>Close department</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_CLOSE_DEP_MANAGEMENT_MODE</LocID>   <Text><![CDATA[Select <b><i>management mode</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_CLOSE_DEP_CLICK</LocID>             <Text><![CDATA[Click on the <b><i>close down department</i></b>.\n\nTip: useful for rebuilding departments, when you need to get rid of patients but keep all the staff.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_DEP_READY</LocID>                   <Text>Department ready</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_DEP_READY_MANAGEMENT_MODE</LocID>   <Text><![CDATA[Select <b><i>management mode</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_DEP_READY_CHECKS</LocID>            <Text><![CDATA[Look at the <b><i>check markers</i></b>, green means everything is OK.\n\nTip: place more than one stretcher to avoid problems.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_DEP_READY_RED_TRIANGLE</LocID>      <Text><![CDATA[<b><i>Red warning signs</i></b> means that you're missing something.\n\nTip: red numbers in rooms and staff shows you what exactly is missing.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_INSURANCE</LocID>                   <Text>Insurance companies</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_INSURANCE_PANEL</LocID>             <Text><![CDATA[Click on <b><i>insurance companies</i></b> button.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_INSURANCE_CONTRACT</LocID>          <Text><![CDATA[Here you can see all insurance companies that can be <b><i>contracted</i></b>.\n\nTip: objectives can unlock the company or provide bonuses.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_INSURANCE_INFO</LocID>              <Text><![CDATA[Every company also shows you, how many <b><i>patients</i></b> they're sending per day.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_INSURANCE_PAYMENT</LocID>           <Text><![CDATA[You can also see a <b><i>payment modifier</i></b> that influences payments for cured patients.\n\nTip: high prestige increases payment modifier.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_INSURANCE_DISABLE</LocID>           <Text><![CDATA[To stop sending patients by certain company, click on the <b><i>disable</i></b> button.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_PRESTIGE</LocID>                    <Text>Prestige</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_PRESTIGE_INFO</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[Prestige is more like overall score of your hospital. <b><i>Low</i></b> prestige decreases amount of patients arriving to your hospital. <b><i>High</i></b> prestige makes higher profit from insurance payments.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_PRESTIGE_MAIN_PANEL</LocID>         <Text><![CDATA[Hover the mouse over <b><i>prestige icon</i></b>.\n\nTip: overall prestige of your hospital is average of departments prestige's plus event bonuses.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_PRESTIGE_MANAGEMENT_MODE</LocID>    <Text><![CDATA[Select <b><i>management mode</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_PRESTIGE_DEPARTMENT</LocID>         <Text><![CDATA[Hover the mouse over <b><i>prestige</i></b> icon on department panel.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_PRESTIGE_DEP_INFO</LocID>           <Text><![CDATA[Here you can see what <b><i>influences</i></b> prestige of your department.\n\nTip: staff and patients overall of their satisfactions]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_SATISFACTION</LocID>                <Text>Satisfaction</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_SATISFACTION_CARD</LocID>           <Text><![CDATA[Click on patient or staff card. <b><i>Satisfaction</i></b> is in the right upper corner.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_SATISFACTION_INFO</LocID>           <Text><![CDATA[Satisfaction represent mood of certain character, hover  mouse over the icon and see all <b><i>modifiers</i></b>.\n\nTip: basic needs are shown above.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_SATISFACTION_HUNGER</LocID>         <Text><![CDATA[<b><i>Hunger</i></b>, make sure you have enough vending machines and dispensers, your staff has fridge in common room, and you have enough nurses to deliver food for hospitalized patients.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_SATISFACTION_BLADDER</LocID>        <Text><![CDATA[<b><i>Bladder</i></b>, you should have enough toilets in sufficient distance for your characters.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_SATISFACTION_REST</LocID>           <Text><![CDATA[<b><i>Rest</i></b>, make sure that your staff is not overload by work, have a common room to rest and enough coffee.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_SATISFACTION_DISCOMFORT</LocID>     <Text><![CDATA[<b><i>Discomfort</i></b>, treat your patients quickly to save them from annoying symptoms.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_SATISFACTION_OTHERS</LocID>         <Text><![CDATA[Other <b><i>modifiers</i></b> are created by environment, procedures and other characters perks.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <!-- ============== -->
            <!--EVENTS ACCIDENTS-->
            <!-- ============== -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>EVENT_HIGHWAY_CRASH</LocID>                         <Text>There has been mass traffic accident on a highway leading to our city. All rescue forces have been dispatched to the crash site. Your hospital should prepare for a high number of seriously wounded patients.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>EVENT_TRAIN_CRASH</LocID>                           <Text>Large train crash! Rescuers are looking through the wreckage and ambulances are transporting the heavily wounded. Hospitals across the county have to prepare for an increased number of seriously injured patients.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>EVENT_CHEMICAL_LEAK</LocID>                         <Text>Dangerous chemicals have leaked from a local chemical plant. Citizens shouldn't go outside or ventilate, ambulances are already transporting a large number of poisoned people to nearby hospitals.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>EVENT_FOOTBALL_GAME</LocID>                         <Text>The clash of fans of two football clubs has caused many injuries. Large number of police officers are handling the situation. Rescuers have treated a large number of patients at the scene, but local hospitals should prepare for an increased number of trauma patients.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>EVENT_BUS_CRASH</LocID>                             <Text>City bus crash! Rescue forces are already on the scene and are treating the wounded. More severe cases are being transported to nearby hospitals.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <!-- ============== -->
            <!--EVENTS EPIDEMIC-->
            <!-- ============== -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>EVENT_FOOD_POISONING</LocID>                        <Text>Food contamination in a local restaurant caused a local epidemic. Even though the health inspectors had closed the restaurant down, all hospitals must to prepare for an increased influx of patients.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>EVENT_SPORTS_CLUB</LocID>                           <Text>Local tourist club got infected and fell ill when traveling abroad. Members are being transported to nearby hospitals staright from the airport.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>EVENT_WATER_PIPES</LocID>                           <Text>The water pipeline accident has contaminated nearly a third of a neighboring city's water supply. Hospitals in the affected area are no longer able to treat new patients and have to transport them to hospitals in a wider area.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>EVENT_ANIMAL_ESCAPE</LocID>                         <Text>The massive escape of animals from a local shelter has caused the spread of various viral and bacterial diseases. The police do not recommend going outside and is asking people who got bitten to immediately report to local hospitals.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>EVENT_FLU_OUTBREAK</LocID>                          <Text>It's flu season again as every year. Doctors are advising people not to underestimate the symptoms and when they start feel really ill, to immediately go to the nearest emergency.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <!-- ============== -->
            <!--EVENTS DISASTERS-->
            <!-- ============== -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>EVENT_FLOODS</LocID>                                <Text>This year's abnormal floods have caused tremendous damage and left many people without access to electricity and supplies. Hospitals should prepare for a large number of various illnesses and the influx of wounded patients.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>EVENT_WINDS</LocID>                                 <Text>Several windstorms have swept over our city, causing extensive damage to property and even lost lives. Many of the wounded and sick are now being transported to nearby hospitals.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>EVENT_EARTHQUAKES</LocID>                           <Text>Massive earthquake that hit the surrounding cities has caused huge damage and cut off thousands of people from help. Rescuers are already transporting the first wounded and sick from the affected areas. Local hospitals should take as many patients as possible.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>EVENT_HEAT</LocID>                                  <Text>A particularly strong heatwave has hit our city. Heart problems, lack of drinking water and spoiled food are the most common causes for ambulance calls in this period.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>EVENT_STOCK_EXCHANGE</LocID>                        <Text>Crash on the stock exchange! Rescuers have seen an unusually high amount of suicide attempts, brain and heart problems.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

        </LocalizedStrings>
    </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
    
