<Database>
    <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_CZ_TUTORIAL">
        
        <LanguageCode>cz</LanguageCode>
        <LanguageNameLocalized>Čeština</LanguageNameLocalized>

        <Contributors>
            <Name>Oxymoron Games</Name>
        </Contributors>
        
        <LocalizedStrings>
            <!--LEVEL 1 - DIAGNOSE: Flow 1-->
            <!--GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_WELCOME</LocID>           <Text>Hi, you are the new doctor right? We are waiting for you. Can you help us with our patient?</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_WELCOME</LocID>           <Text>Hi boss, we're having some staff issues at the clinic, could you help us with a few patients?\nOh, don't worry, I'll remind you how everything works here.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_ZOOM_IN</LocID>           <Text><![CDATA[First let's have a closer look to see what's going on. You can <b><i>zoom in</i></b> out with the mouse wheel and pan by holding down the middle mouse button.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_WALL_CONFIGURATION</LocID><Text><![CDATA[You can also notice that all walls are up, kinda blocking the view. <b><i>Change</i></b> the view to your liking.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_SELECT_PATIENT</LocID>    <Text><![CDATA[Exelent, now <b><i>select the patient</i></b> who's been patiently waiting for us in the doctor's office.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_PATIENT_CARD</LocID>      <Text>This is the patient's card. It will give you all the important information and you can control what happens with your patients from here.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_LAST_SELECTED</LocID>     <Text>On the right side you'll find the history of the last 6 selected characters.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_PORTRAIT</LocID>          <Text>If you click the portrait of any character, the camera will center on them.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_PATIENTS_CONTROL</LocID>  <Text>You can choose who is responsible for your patient. Either you let your staff take care of them or you can take over directly. Let's keep this patient under your control.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_NEEDS_PANEL</LocID>       <Text>The upper part of the card shows you the patient's personal data and department assignment. The needs panel on the right shows the satisfaction level and you can see character's perks and quirks bellow that.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_DIAGNOSES</LocID>         <Text>The next panel shows all possible diagnoses that match patient's known symptoms, ordered from the most likely one. Selecting a diagnosis will set it as the final one.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_SYMPTOMS</LocID>          <Text>The symptoms panel shows all revealed and hidden symptoms. On the left you can see the doctor the patient is currently assigned to.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_EXAMINATIONS</LocID>      <Text><![CDATA[This is the examination panel where you can order examinations to reveal what the hidden symptoms are. Try to <b><i>select Nasal cavity inspection</i></b> to reveal enough hidden symptoms so there's only one possible diagnosis left.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_PATIENT_DIAGNOSED</LocID> <Text><![CDATA[You can see which finished examinations revealed a symptom, the ones that did are highlighted in green. Now go ahead and <b><i>select the one diagnosis that's left.</i></b>]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_TREATMENTS</LocID>        <Text><![CDATA[Now nothing stops us from treating the patient. You can hover over the icon of your selected diagnosis to see a tooltip which will suggest the correct treatment. Go ahead and <b><i>choose the treatment.</i></b>]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_GOOD_JOB</LocID>          <Text>Good job, you treated your first patient. Depending on the selected treatment, your patient will be either cured or might return later with new symptoms.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_CONTINUE</LocID>          <Text>Click next to continue the tutorial.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <!--LEVEL 1 - DIAGNOSE: Flow 2-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_OPEN_CARD</LocID>         <Text><![CDATA[Let's move to the next patient. <b><i>Click the patient that is sitting in the doctor's office.</i></b>]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_COMPLICATED_CASE</LocID>  <Text>You probably noticed earlier that some examinations are not available (grey). They need special rooms or equipment.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_MISSING_STUFF</LocID>     <Text>If you mouse over the greyed icon, a tooltip will tell you what is missing. In this case we are missing both the room and a lab technologist to be able to run the X-Ray.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_TOOLTIP</LocID>           <Text>There's a tooltip with extra information for every icon in every category.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_FIX_MISSING_STUFF</LocID> <Text>So for now, let us fix the hospital real quick.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <!--LEVEL 1 - DIAGNOSE: Flow 3-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_FIXED</LocID>             <Text><![CDATA[Now everything should be in order and when you <b><i>open the patients card again, you can select the now available examination.</i></b>]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_BOOKMARK</LocID>          <Text>If you want to be kept in the loop, you must keep the patient under your care or in favorites. The same icon switches between all the modes.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_BOOKMARKED</LocID>        <Text>Right now the patient is under you care, just as we want.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_CARD_OPTIONS</LocID>      <Text>The card can be closed by the X in the upper right corner. Or you can pin them if you would like to keep an eye on the patient every step of the way.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_TIME_MANIPULATION</LocID> <Text><![CDATA[This examination will take some time. You can <b><i>fast forward the game time</i></b> using the controls in the middle of the main panel.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_WAITING_FOR_RESULTS</LocID><Text>Let's watch what happens with our patient. You can even skip one hour ahead.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_STAT_LAB_RESULTS</LocID>  <Text>The popup notification is informing you that the X-Ray has revealed a symptom.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_POP_UP</LocID>            <Text>You can change the way how you want to receive notifications by switching it to 'pop-up' or 'log' in the lower left corner of the message window.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_POP_UP_CLOSE</LocID>      <Text>By clicking OK you can close the notification.</Text></GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_LOG</LocID>               <Text>You can reopen the messages from the log panel in the bottom right of the screen.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_FINAL_DIAGNOSE</LocID>    <Text>The last examination provided by the X-Ray revealed a symptom unique to the patient's disease. The diagnosis is now clear, with a 100% probability.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_PRIORITIES</LocID>        <Text>Usually running tests (rentgen, stat lab) is the most certain way to confirm a diagnosis, but they also take a lot of time.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_OBJECTIVES</LocID>        <Text><![CDATA[Now when you dusted off the basics, its time for your first real objective. Treat 5 patients. <b><i>Finish it.</i></b>]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_TUTORIAL_1_FINISHED</LocID><Text><![CDATA[Awesome you have done it. Thank you for your help! We can take over from here I think you are needed elsewhere. <b><i>Click next to finish the level.</i></b>]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <!--LEVEL 2 - BUILDING: Flow 1-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HELLO</LocID>           <Text>Welcome to this nice property we recently acquired! Let's look at how to build and equip your very own hospital and what options there are.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_BUILDING_MODE</LocID>   <Text><![CDATA[Alright, let's build a nice little clinic first! Let's switch to building mode. You can <b><i>click the button in the top left corner</i></b> of the screen or just push the F6 key.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_FOUNDATIONS</LocID>     <Text><![CDATA[The first important step is laying down foundations. The foundations tool is selected already - <b><i>cover an area big enough to house at least 3 rooms</i></b> (min 20x20 tiles).]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_CATEGORIES</LocID>      <Text>Excellent! Now here's a quick summary of what's available to build. There are 5 main categories: foundations, constructions, doors and windows, objects and prefabs.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_SUB_CATEGORIES</LocID>  <Text>Each category is further divided into subcategories. Don't forget there's a tooltip for each category and item with more info!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_LOGISTICS</LocID>       <Text><![CDATA[Now that we have a place to build, we need to design our floor plan. The very basic unit of every hospital is emergency. <b><i>Please select management mode</i></b> to see which rooms we'll definitely need to make the department operational.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_LOGISTICS_ROOMS</LocID> <Text><![CDATA[The list is divided between mandatory and optional rooms. <b><i>Let's place all three rooms</i></b>, these are needed for a working clinic.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_BUILD_WALLS</LocID>     <Text><![CDATA[Well done! With the floor plan done, <b><i>let's build some walls</i></b>. You can find them in the building mode under construction category]]>.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_WALLS_INFO</LocID>      <Text>Great! Walls are often not required for the rooms to function, but some objects need to be hanged on a wall.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_WALLS_ADDITIONAL_INFO</LocID><Text>You can also choose wall color and whether you build walls in a line or in a rectangle pattern. The different options of each tool are always at the bottom of the building mode.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_FLOOR_INFO</LocID>      <Text><![CDATA[You can also build various types of floors, doors and windows. When you are happy with your setup <b><i>click next</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_SELECT_ROOM</LocID>     <Text><![CDATA[Let's focus on furnishing the rooms now. Simply <b><i>click on the floor</i></b> of any of the rooms.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_EQUIPMENT_INFO</LocID>  <Text>Now the panel shows furniture and equipment that is either mandatory (orange) or optional (yellow) for the room. You can rotate objects by pressing R or middle mouse button. Or cancel selection by Right mouse button.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_EQUIPMENT_ADDITIONAL_INFO</LocID><Text>Some objects need additional equipment to work. If the object in scene is yellow you can hover over it and see what equipment it needs. It will be blue in euipment panel.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_EQUIPMENT_OBJECTIVE</LocID><Text><![CDATA[Now <b><i>equip your rooms</i></b>.\nArrows on objects are access points for characters (grey) and objects (green). Don't forget to place doors so your rooms and buildings are accessible to patients.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_OPTIONAL_EQUIPMENT</LocID><Text>The optional equipment usually contains decorations or objects that don't serve a particular purpose in the given room, but improve the environment.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_PREFABS_CATEGORY</LocID><Text><![CDATA[Now let's have a look at the last category and a great timesaver - prefabs. Select the <b><i>prefabs category</i></b> in the building mode.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_PREFAB_CATEGORY_SELECTED</LocID><Text><![CDATA[Now, you can see the different rooms divided by departments. Choose any of the prefabs and place it into an unoccupied area in your clinic.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_PREFAB_PLACED</LocID>    <Text>You now placed a fully equipped room - it's also automatically added to the floor plan. You can of course modify it to exactly fit your needs.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_TUTORIAL_2_FINISHED</LocID><Text>Well done! This part is finished.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
           
            <!--LEVEL 3 - MANAGEMENT: Flow 1-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_WELCOME_MANAGEMENT</LocID><Text>Welcome to our third tutorial focused on Project Hospital management. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_DEPARTMENT_CARD_OPEN</LocID> <Text><![CDATA[Let us have a closer look at Department management. Go ahead and <b><i>open it</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_DEPARTMENT_CARD_INFO</LocID><Text>Here you will always find the infomation about selected department. Number of staff, rooms their satisfcaction. And most importantly functionality - keep an eye on the red triangles and numbers.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_CHIEF_INFO</LocID><Text>In staff panel you can choose Chief doc and chief nurse. Be carefull when selecting them, because they can improve or worsen overall productivity of your employees.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_CERTAINTY</LocID><Text>Next very important thing that you can adjust is “certainty” level. It represents value how carefull the doctors are when selecting final diagnosis.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_EMPLOYEES</LocID><Text>The last part will tell you about how many workplaces you have occupied by your employees and their overall satisfaction. Pay attention to their needs.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_PATIENTS_PANEL</LocID><Text>In patients panel you can find various information about your patients in general. Their statictics and needs. Keep an eye on that because too much unhappy patients can lower prestige of your hospital.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_ROOMS_PANEL</LocID><Text>Rooms panel gives you informations about department's rooms. You can check their state: built, missing and recommended. You can easily check by color that they are either OK(green) or missing somethig (grey).</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_VALIDATION_PANEL</LocID><Text>Last panel is department validation panel. It gives you quick summary about your missing things in department.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HIRING</LocID><Text><![CDATA[Let's have a look at your Hiring options. <b><i>Click on the Hiring button</i></b> in your desired departments card.]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HIRING_SELECTED</LocID><Text>Here you can hire any staff you need or want. There are four categories - doctors, nurses, lab specialists and janitors. Be carefull when making proper choice. You can check their levels, skills, perks and their required salary. </Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HIRING_OPTIONS</LocID><Text>Character selection is tied to selected department. So if you have selected for example Neurology department you will able to choose from Neurologist, not from Cardiologists.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HIRING_AGENCY</LocID><Text>You can also choose you staff trough “Hiring agency”, if you dont like the current rooster. But remember that this step will cost you some money.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HIRE_EMPLOYEE_INFO</LocID><Text>To hire any employee, just click on desired portrait and drop employee into hospital. Employee will be assigned automatically to the nearest workplace. You can also assign the workplace from employee card.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HIRE_EMPLOYEE_TASK</LocID><Text><![CDATA[Hire a <b><i>doctor for emergency department</i></b> and <b><i>a lab technologist for radiology department</i></b>.\n\nTip: You can switch department at the bottom left of the main panel.]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_LOGISTICS_SELECT</LocID><Text><![CDATA[Now you can check their assigned workspaces. <b><i>Select management mode</i></b>.]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_WORKSPACES</LocID><Text>Workspaces constist from desk, chair and pc as you know by now. And you can see they are now occupied (on your selected department). You can also select empty workspace and hire employee that way.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_EMPLOYEE_CARD</LocID><Text><![CDATA[Let's have a closer look at your staff. <b><i>Open any of your employees card</i></b>.]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_EMPLOYEE_CARD_LEVELS</LocID><Text>Every employee is defined by their level, skills and specializations. For lab specialists and nurses there are three levels, doctors could be at five levels. Levels provide choice of different specializations.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_EMPLOYEE_CARD_SKILLS</LocID><Text>Skills are fixed for each type of personel, but could be improved by training them in practice. More about individual skills you can learn from icon pop-ups.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_EMPLOYEE_CARD_SPECIALIZATIONS</LocID><Text>Specializations give opportunity of work at certain places, departments, rooms; docs are able to provide specific examinations or treatments. For example doctor with cardiology can not provide special neurology procedures.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_EMPLOYEE_CARD_SECOND_SPECIALIZATION</LocID><Text>Employees can have one or two specializations. First one categorize selected doctor to some department. After leveling in that specialization you will able to select the second one.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_NIGHT_SHIFT</LocID><Text><![CDATA[In Project Hospital you can maintain your very own hospital operational 24/7. To achieve this you need to manage day and night shifts. <b><i>Click on “night shift” button</i></b>]]>.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_NIGHT_SHIFT_INFO</LocID><Text>All workplaces are unoccupied. To maintain your hospital open during night you need to hire characters for night shifts. In advanced stages of the game it will give you opportunity to hospitalize patients.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_NEW_DEPARTMENT</LocID><Text><![CDATA[Now we will show you how to add new department. Open <b><i>Hospital managment - departments section</i></b> by clicking on it's icon]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_ADD_DEPARTMENT</LocID><Text><![CDATA[Here you can add various departments to grow your hospital or remove them, when you don't want them longer to use. <b><i>Add new department</i></b>.]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_INSURANCE_COMPANY</LocID><Text><![CDATA[Well done! Now we will take a look at your patients income. <b><i>Open Insurance section</i></b> of the hospital management card.]]></Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_INSURANCE_COMPANY_OPENED</LocID><Text>Here you can see overview of Insurance companies. You can contract them, or release them. Each of them is specific.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_INSURANCE_COMPANY_INFO</LocID><Text>Each sends to you hospital certain amount of patients, pays you certain amount of money and can vary with the complicated cases and diagnoses. You can accomplish various objectives and get some bonuses and rewards.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_TUTORIAL_3_FINISHED</LocID><Text>In short that is all about our intoduction to Project Hospital management.</Text> </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <!--LEVEL 4 - HOSPITALIZATION: Flow 1-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_WELCOME_HOSPITALIZATION</LocID><Text>Welcome to our last tutorial focused on Hospitalization process.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HOSPITAL_OVERVIEW</LocID><Text>This can start on Emergency deparment with Observation or Trauma hospitalization.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HOSPITAL_OBSERVATION</LocID><Text>Patient is sent to observation room if there is no clear diagnosis and patitent needs proper medical care. Once the diagnosis is clear, patient is sent home or hospitalized to respective department.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HOSPITAL_OBSERVATION_SEND</LocID><Text><![CDATA[Let's have a look at the patient in the scene. <b><i>Select him and send him to observation room</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HOSPITAL_OBSERVATION_SENT</LocID><Text>If the patient is assigned to Observation room examinations will be done by on-call room staff, and your doctor in doctor's office can take another case.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HOSPITAL_TRAUMA_CENTER_OVERVIEW</LocID><Text>Trauma center is essential unit for handling different types of traumas and accidents. It is highly equipped examination room designed for acquiring maximum effort to stabilize patient for his further treatment.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HOSPITAL_TRAUMA_CENTER_INFO</LocID><Text>Trauma center works the same way as observation room. As long as the diagnose is not clear patient will remain here. So it's best to work fast, so your Trauma center will not be blocked for other patiens.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_DEPARTMENT_HOSPITALIZATION</LocID><Text>With clear diagnosis are patients hospitalized to respective departments. Every department has two types of Inpatient rooms. For Normal or High hospitalization.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_NORMAL_HOSPITALIZATION</LocID><Text>Regular ward is suitable for patients with regular diagnoses, when there is almost none risk of some life threatening condition appearing.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HIGH_HOSPITALIZATION</LocID><Text>High Dependency Unit is suitable for patients, where you can expect appearance or presence of some life threatening condition. They are generally equiped with life monitor to observe vital function of patients.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_ICU_HOSPITALIZATION</LocID><Text>Now you know about couple types of hospitalization, but there is one more option. If patient's stance is crirical and life threatening he will be sent to Intensive Care Unit - ICU. </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_DOCTORS_ROUNDS</LocID><Text>In Project hospital there is 24/7 patient care (you can check the schedule). Doctors at departments providing daily so called “Doctor's round”, during which they visit patients and prescribe additional examination for them.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_NURSES_CHECKUPS</LocID><Text>Nurses are providing Nurses checkups (more often the higher hospitalization level). They can notice and warn you about new hidden symptom appearing in any patient. twice a day.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_NURSES_MEDICINE_LUNCH</LocID><Text>Nurses also deliver medicine - patients take it twice a day. And last but not least - every hospitalized patient has his meal every day…if your nurses station is equipped with food cart.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_DEATH</LocID><Text>...and when something goes really wrong? Well, everything has its end. But death could be turned on or off. When you turn it ON, your patients will die sometimes. When you turn it OFF your partients will be transfered away.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_HOSPITALIZATION_END</LocID><Text>So this is it! In short, of course. There are many aspects of Project Hospital that are awaiting you! Godspeed!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <!--BENCHMARK-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>LEVEL_BENCHMARK</LocID><Text>Benchmark</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_BENCHMARK</LocID><Text>Benchmark is running, this will only be a second!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>TUTORIAL_TEXT_BENCHMARK_DONE</LocID><Text>Benchmark is done! Please take a screenshot before clicking next.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <!--INGAME TUTORIALS-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_BUILDING</LocID>                    <Text>Building foundations</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_BUILDING_MODE</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[Select <b><i>building mode</i></b>.\n\nTip: mostly useful width of rooms is 6 tiles and for corridors 4 tiles, so recommended width of building is 16 tiles.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_BUILDING_FOUNDATION_TOOLS</LocID>   <Text><![CDATA[Go to the <b><i>foundation tools</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_BUILDING_FOUDATIONS</LocID>         <Text><![CDATA[Click on <b><i>building foundations</i></b> icon and drag mouse over required area.\n\nTip: foundations can be removed only by dynamite tool.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_BUILDING_CONSTRUCTION_TOOLS</LocID> <Text><![CDATA[Go to <b><i>construction tools</i></b>.]]></Text>   </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_BUILDING_WALLS</LocID>              <Text><![CDATA[Click on <b><i>walls</i></b>.\n\nTip: at the very bottom of panel are other tools for wall placing or removing.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_BUILDING_MATERIAL</LocID>           <Text><![CDATA[Select required <b><i>material</i></b> and drag to create walls or replace their materials.\n\nTip: at the bottom of panel you can change color of the most of patterns.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_BUILDING_WINDOORS</LocID>           <Text><![CDATA[Click on <b><i>doors and windows</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_BUILDING_WINDOORS_PLACE</LocID>     <Text><![CDATA[Place required <b><i>doors and windows</i></b>.\n\nTip: at the bottom of panel you can change colors.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_LAYOUT</LocID>                      <Text>Building layout</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_LAYOUT_MANAGEMENT_MODE</LocID>      <Text><![CDATA[Select <b><i>management mode</i></b>.\n\nTip: at the very bottom of panel are tools for changing access to your rooms.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_LAYOUT_PLACEMENT</LocID>            <Text><![CDATA[In the clinic or hospital parts click on required <b><i>room</i></b> and drag it into your building.\n\nTip: don't forget to place walls and doors for your new rooms.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>            
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_EQUIPMENT</LocID>                   <Text>Room equipment</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_EQUIPMENT_BUILDING_MODE</LocID>     <Text><![CDATA[Select <b><i>building mode</i></b> and by right click cancel current tool.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_EQUIPMENT_ROOM_SELECT</LocID>       <Text><![CDATA[On the floors you can see white icons of your <b><i>rooms</i></b>. Choose one and click\n\nTip: in the corners of rooms are messages telling you what is missing.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>            
            <!--TODO text below is too long needs to be shorter-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_EQUIPMENT_PANEL</LocID>             <Text><![CDATA[Equipment panel shows you all mandatory (red), recommended (yellow), and optional <b><i>objects</i></b>.\n\nTip: hover mouse around yellow objects in room, blue frame shows what's missing.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_EQUIPMENT_DECORATIONS</LocID>       <Text><![CDATA[Click on <b><i>decorations</i></b>. Here you can find decorative objects and place it to your rooms.you should place in.\n\nTip: decorative objects can improve mood of characters in the room.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_EQUIPMENT_DECALS</LocID>            <Text><![CDATA[Click on <b><i>decals</i></b>. Here you can select and use wall decals.\n\nTip: at the bottom of panel you can change color of the decals.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>            
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_HIRING</LocID>                      <Text>Hiring new staff</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_HIRING_MANAGEMENT_MODE</LocID>      <Text><![CDATA[Select <b><i>management mode</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_HIRING_BUTTON</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[Click on the new <b><i>staff</i></b> button.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_HIRING_PROFESSION</LocID>           <Text><![CDATA[Choose what <b><i>profession</i></b> do you need.\n\nTip: to know required specialization, hover the mouse over the staff on management panel a read the tooltip.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_HIRING_SHIFTS</LocID>               <Text><![CDATA[Choose day or night <b><i>shift</i></b>.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>      <LocID>INGAME_TUTORIAL_HIRING_SELECTION</LocID>            <Text><![CDATA[Select required <b><i>character</i></b> and place them into rooms they should work.\n\nTip: after placement the character will automatically find the nearest workspace.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            

        </LocalizedStrings>
    </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
    